Huge announcement.
I have been selected.
One of the few in the world to represent my country and participate in the Beast Games.
It's not true.
I lied.
It's a lie.
Imagine that, though.
Imagine I pop up on the Beast Games and I just stand there, you know?
That was so weird.
I can't believe it.
I actually haven't watched Beast Games, so I don't even know what it's about.
I just know that it's like... like over the top, right?
Very over the top stuff.
What's going on, people?
I have been Mr. Beast all along.
Yeah, Persona 5 music, man.
Yeah, it's so good.
This one is from Mementos.
Oh, yeah.
I've got my Danish water next to me.
My hands are hot, meaning not cold.
Which means, today, I will actually just win.
I cannot physically lose.
I have no excuses.
Oliver Live, I'll study a different day.
No!
You go back to studying.
Unless, you know, you have time.
Then it's okay, you can stay.
But if it's like tomorrow, then no, go study, you know?
I'm really good at giving advice.
I'm terrible at following it myself.
I was one of those that always did everything on the last day and it was not good for my mental health back then.
I managed to get through it with that strategy, though.
That's such a great idea, genius France.
We should do a warm up run in Isaac before we play Isaac.
What do you think?
Just to get ready for the game, you know?
I know what you mean, though.
You mean the character, right?
Yeah.
I have not read or seen Project Hail Mary yet.
I wanted to go watch it, but I don't really have anyone to watch it with right now.
I could go alone, which is, you know, it's fine.
I just haven't done it.
I've heard great things about it.
I'm looking forward to it.
We don't get enough sci-fi these days, man.
I'm so excited for any sci-fi.
No randomizer today?
Wait, what does that mean?
Randomizer?
Oh, you're talking about random characters.
I think so.
Yeah, we're going to do some random randomization for sure.
Yeah.
Red is my favorite color.
That is correct.
Dunya Krishna.
Hey, what's up, Louis Topher?
First livestream?
Still in episode 3050 of the first Minecraft... Dude, first Minecraft playthrough is still, you know, bringing in people.
I can't believe it.
That's like... I had no idea that would become so big when I started playing that.
It was more like an off... Ah, fine.
Let's... I don't know what to do today.
Let me throw up Minecraft, you know, in livestream.
One of the first livestreams I ever did on YouTube as well.
Just, you know, see how it went.
I can't believe it got so popular.
It's blowing my mind.
I'm glad you liked it, though.
Yeah, recently TikTok has been signal boosting it like crazy.
I don't even know who's making the TikToks, but someone out there is making the TikToks.
And that's pretty cool, I guess.
Yeah, the second season is definitely a little different than the first.
The machine.
Yep.
I know that took a long time, but man, I don't regret a thing.
That was so much fun to make.
Is today the Rage Bait stream?
You know what, actually, yes.
Today I'm going to intentionally Rage Bait.
I've been looking forward to this for a while.
So you'll probably notice it when it happens, but instead of my usual unintentional Rage Bait, we will actually do it intentionally today.
It's gonna be fun.
I will try to make you as mad as possible, unless we succeed.
We're gonna check the YouTube comments on the VOD, see if it works.
Please don't do this to me.
I feel like if I do a intentional Rage Bait stream, it's gonna be somehow less Rage Bait-y than an unintentional one.
But that's just my, you know, thinking.
I don't know.
You do that every day, though.
But it's not intentional.
I try not to Rage Bait too much, but I just have this, you know, like, I don't know, organ inside of me.
Like, my body is a Rage Bait-producing machine.
I can't stop the machine.
It needs to go on and on, you know?
The pumps are going, the wheels are turning.
Once it starts, you can't stop it.
Never forget this.
I'm not gonna radio.
Okay, that one... Listen.
That one became a little Rage Bait-y at some point.
I will admit that I definitely did a little intentional Rage Bait with that.
But it was not Rage Bait at the time.
I thought it was a fun, practical joke, you know?
I don't think people even used that word back then.
Back then, it's like a couple of years ago.
It's not even that long ago.
Animal well, that wasn't Rage Bait.
I honestly don't recall which parts.
Like, you just mean the entire playthrough?
No, it was not Rage Bait.
My body is a machine that turns bait into rage.
I feel like I'm the opposite.
When I get mad, I start to bait.
Unintentionally.
It's like a symbiosis we have going on here.
Dude, I'm so ready for the new Subnautica 2 tray.
I can't wait.
I've been thinking about Subnautica lately, actually.
Kinda wanted to play it again.
The first one.
I prefer the first one slightly to the second one.
Or the, you know, expansion.
Can you show your nose to the game?
Yes, I can.
There you go.
I need to.
Good thing you reminded me, by the way.
I gotta play Lazarus to unlock a new character.
See what he sees, do what he does, follow the dark.
Oh, we got this from that machine.
I was like, why did I write that?
I see now.
Go to angel looking church area and dig on the X.
I feel like that one, we're gonna put that in parenthesis for now.
I'm not happy about this one too much.
Bring him the photo.
This one is kind of big, I think.
Always head in the clouds.
This one could also be big.
I think it's related to going up to heaven.
You know, head in the clouds.
Lazarus to unlock a new character.
Right.
We are definitely gonna do that today.
If the randomization gods allow it.
We're also gonna do greed mode today and challenges.
We're gonna do a little bit of everything.
Just to get back into things, you know?
Ease into it.
Alright, let's go.
I'm excited.
Also, let me... Oh, I did remove the overlay.
Good.
Good stuff.
Oh,
you can't see.
And... Oh my god, that was delayed.
I snapped my finger six times.
What the hell was that?
Jesus.
Alright.
You know what, actually?
Let's start things off here with greed mode.
Yes.
Let's do a greed mode.
Greed mode.
Random.
No.
We're gonna do a greed mode as sasyl to start things off.
Let's do it.
Greed mode as sasyl.
I am just excited to shoot some lasers, guys.
Okay?
Don't... What did I just do?
Oh, something just dropped.
Somehow.
I'm gonna maybe grab that.
Yeah, I'll take that.
Now I gotta remember how to do this.
The good news is we can fly.
Alright.
Grab the key.
We can actually re-roll, but I think we can always re-roll, so maybe that's not a big surprise.
Why did I react like that?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm intentionally rage baiting.
This is the day where I intentionally rage bait.
Oh yeah, I can't access this yet.
Sikes!
Come on now.
That was too easy, wasn't it?
Matchbook, I will take it.
The full... Oh, damn.
Let me see here.
Three bombs, matchstick trinket, and the blackheart.
Dude, I'm kind of rolling in hearts right now.
This is a great start.
We can even go in here.
Okay.
What is that?
Chemical peel?
Increases the damage of tears fired from Isaac's left eye.
Notice how that did not affect the stats at all.
So maybe the right eye is what the stats reflect.
Left eye is not being reflected in the stats.
It's like a separate thing.
That's what I think.
I think it's time we go.
Bring it on.
Don't you dare.
Guys, you ever have it like when you're visiting your parents or something, right?
Because I just did that.
And when you're there, you're like, oh, this is cool.
I like it.
But whenever you come home, you always have this feeling that when you finally sit in your own chair in front of your computer, you're like, ah, man, that is... there's just nothing like it.
You know, sitting in that chair in front of your computer is just magical.
In Denmark, we have a saying, Ulgot menjemebist, which means it's good out, but it's best at home.
And that couldn't be more true.
Destroy that guy.
Oh, you!
Wow, that was actually massively dodged.
And you can't argue with me.
Get out of here.
Oh, no.
Come on.
Are you gonna charge me?
Stop him before he charges.
The best defense is good offense, as Wolverine said.
Why is the music still playing?
Shouldn't the music stop now that we finished the encounter?
Maybe not.
So we have coupon.
Makes one item in the shop or Devil Room 3.
Oh, this is actually such a good item for this.
Holding this item passively guarantees that one item in the shop.
Dude, that is actually fantastic.
Okay,
so this one is on sale now.
And if I click this, we can get one of these to be free.
Oh, magic scab.
Please let it be magic scab.
Go!
Not the key!
Okay, that's super unlucky.
That is actually crazy.
Oh, well.
That's fine.
We're gonna be using this quite a bit as we go on.
Oh, wait, I have the fool.
We can go in here.
Hey!
Not bad, huh?
Pause time.
This guy makes laser?
Yep.
Wait, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Okay.
Don't do it.
Don't even think about it.
Kill him!
Nice.
Not bad.
Dude, I'm kinda owning it right now.
I'm happy about this.
We're taking this.
Absolutely.
We have a box.
Spongebob, Red Heart, Key Bomb, Coin Pill, Cart or Rune.
And a trinket.
I mean, maybe we'll do it.
Wait, what was that?
Oh, I thought a guy was standing in the corner just menacingly.
But he's hanging.
That just actually made my skin crawl a little bit.
Oh, jeez.
I mean, Azazel is actually just so good.
And look at this, Devil Deal?
The Book of Belial.
Ooh, that is also good.
But is it better than what I have?
The coupon is kind of made for greed mode, in my opinion.
So what about that one?
Enemy from behind?
I mean, with the laser, it's gonna be really good.
I think I want this.
That's a good trade.
The other one?
Not so much.
Yeah, I think we're done here.
Ah, wait, secret doors?
Yeah.
Nice.
Oh, it's going swimmingly.
Can't ask for more.
Oh, look at this.
We got a secret rock.
And more blue hearts?
Damn.
No way!
Azazel is blast!
No, I used the key on the key thingy.
Ah, I gotcha, didn't I?
Rage bait achieved.
You thought I did that on purpose?
I did.
I mean, you know what I mean.
That was on purpose, guys.
I got you.
Yep.
There we go.
I'm willing to sacrifice.
Ooh, range is really good for me.
Range is fantastic.
We take that.
Let's see what we have on offer here.
This one's on sale.
Wait, get out of here.
Oh, I can also open that, except I can't.
The extra range right now is massive.
Key is huge.
Oh, the converter!
I need to buy it.
I need to buy that.
Oh, my God.
Wait, that's a blue fly to the jar.
Oh, I don't like this one.
It's another active, though.
Wish I could reroll this.
If only I had a certain item.
Nah, I don't want it, actually.
I don't want that.
I say no to that.
I disregard.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah, I take damage on that.
Have to remember.
Oh, I got to try the backstabbing.
This probably counts as backstab back there.
I mean, just look at the speed here.
If you want to speedrun this game as Azazel, which I'm going to do today, by the way, we're going to try a speedrun on Azazel today, like in the normal game mode, you know?
I've been wanting to do that for a while.
He's like the obvious character for that.
Time is on my side.
Nice.
I'm not falling for the little bone tricks.
Man, I'm powerful.
Twenty-six gold in the bank.
You know what I'm buying.
Except, wait a sec.
Speed tiers.
Less damage, though.
Damage down, multiplier.
Ah, but it's going to take us to two out of three on fungi.
Could be worth it.
This one.
Oh, wait, let me.
No.
Wait, am I reading this right?
Makes one item in the shop.
Oh, my God.
Is that for real?
Okay, well, it happens.
I'm open this.
I'm rich!
I buy everything.
I take this, convert, and PhD.
Feels two red hearts, converts back.
Oh, that's nice.
I'll be buying that.
Let me have a burp.
Gives a copy of the last pill taken.
Oh.
Wait, so I'm going to get a copy of the pill I... Hmm.
What is the last pill I took?
I think that was the one that did nothing for me.
Maybe not good.
Mom's box spawns a trinket?
That's really good, except it's another active.
Maybe it will go with the odd mushroom.
I'm not sure.
This one, we're going to spawn a trinket.
We're going to gain luck, though.
Surely that's good.
Ah, but that's only when we have it equipped, right?
Is that what I think it is?
Oh, I think we got to do that.
The diaper.
Okay.
Unfortunately, we can't do it yet.
I'm going to charge this one up, because it's important to have charges on this guy.
This is what I bring to the next floor, by the way.
Because it's just that important.
Let's try and backstab him!
Okay.
How bad?
When does the back... Oh, that's the backstab right there!
15, 15, 15, 15.
Do it!
Ah, man.
I'm going to do it.
Ah, should I?
Yeah, let's do it.
We're doing it.
So let me just see again.
Visually distorts entities in the room, grants a small stat increase or decrease, and grants the fruitcake effect for the room.
Item pedestals are rerolled into glitched items.
You know what?
I'm going to do it in this room.
Ketsumajima!
Ramming speed!
Okay.
Wait.
Ramming speed?
Okay, we have an objective.
We got to figure out what this is.
Mary Jane Mister.
Something.
Let's try and pay attention to the environment.
What is different?
Has something changed?
It's like I'm looking for a glitch in the matrix.
The cat walks by twice, you know?
There's also this thing.
More options?
Oh!
Really want to buy that one, actually.
Do want to charge this one up one more time.
Let's just get a bit of energy on it.
A hundred percent demon!
Let's keep it that way.
Hey!
Maybe kill the little guys.
Come here.
Oh, you're jumping!
Don't shoot.
Oh yeah, I can't take damage from the creep.
I have to remember.
Oh wait, you're not dead.
I thought you were dead, son.
We got the devil room.
What's that?
The pact.
Oh, that's good.
We got to take it.
That's an easy W right there.
No hesitation on my part.
We even get money.
The state can't get any better.
It's incredible.
Okay, let's see here.
I did not... Oh, it's only one charge I got from that.
Wow.
Maybe it's okay with the black hearts.
I don't really need to go too crazy here.
Odd mushroom.
Six coins.
I could go in here as well, but I'm gonna lose a heart if I do.
A black heart, which is not ideal.
Guess I'll... Oh, what was this battery thing?
Probably recharges the health active item on... Oh, okay.
Hold on now.
That could actually be worth.
We just need one more coin.
Yeah, we need to buy that actually.
That's huge.
No!
We're done on the floor.
Okay, I'm going in here.
No, there's nothing.
Maybe secret room here?
It's got to be here.
Yeah, there we go.
Uh, Kisha.
And Moonjoy.
Hi.
Okay.
Weird.
We're gonna buy it.
Fully man it up.
Don't tell me it was the heart.
You gotta be shitting me.
Come on.
Okay, uh, Isaac's bombs didn't affect... Nah, I don't like that very much.
Let's do another one.
Wait, why can I pick this again?
Wait, I'm so... Hold on a minute.
Oh, it's not the same item.
Oh, I was so confused.
It's a different one.
Ah, gotcha with the rage bait, didn't I?
Ha ha.
Gotcha.
We're gonna take this now.
More options, of course.
That's, that's a massive W.
Mom's Fox.
What was that one again?
Oh, we're out of mana on that.
You know what?
I can take this and do this.
Conversion!
And then we take this and then we move on.
Yeah, I could also take this, but I don't want... I think the diaper is maybe better.
Yeah, Skatol effect is kind of good.
I like Skatol.
Could also reroll.
Wait, if I reroll, I wonder if that rerolls the items on the pedestals here that are free.
Wait a minute.
Ah, okay, okay.
Fine.
Too bad.
It was a good attempt, though.
I'll take this pill.
Yes, we'll bring it with me.
Well, we're poor now.
Moving on.
Okay, immediately go to this room.
A lump of coal or the amaze.
Dude, this item is fucking cracked.
This has to be one of the best items in the game.
Like, it's not even close.
Okay, maybe the brimstone is, you know, up there, but that item is for sure... goated.
We literally cannot lose.
Kamen and Sazal W unlock once again.
Oh, thank you.
We can even get two hearts now.
Watch.
Just one.
But we are full on hearts now.
I mean, pretty good, huh?
Torn photo is actually not too bad.
Get some stats.
Nice.
Ah, I got you with the rage bait!
That was intentional.
I told you we're going to do that today.
Every time I make a mistake, it is actually intentional and it has always been.
I am secretly a professional Isaac player.
You didn't know this, but it's true.
I have been competing in the Olympics.
Or whatever it's called.
I know all the tricks.
Dude, my damage is up there!
Look at that!
I just have to touch them and they die.
Feels so good.
Don't even shoot.
What the hell was that?
Oh, that's got to be my glitched item!
I think?
Does that look glitch AF?
We're done.
Also, we have 8 out of 10 on coins right now.
I don't know what that means.
Wait.
Is it maybe the coins that we have left when we go to the new floor gets added to that?
Ah, that may be the case, actually.
11 coins now.
Still no key.
Oh, I could buy a key.
Because there's going to be two items in that room.
It's going to be worth it.
Where are we going here?
Aha!
Huh?
Not bad.
Is that Spider-bot?
No, it's Spider-Bite.
He has to fire slowing tears, increases with luck.
We have good luck.
That, I don't know what is.
It looks like an active item and I don't like that.
Oh, also, I just remembered...
Nah, this is the unlockiest coupon of all time.
But...
Come on, be good to me.
Yeah!
That's how we do it in Kansas, baby.
If you try enough, you will succeed.
I'm going to take this guy.
It's not an active.
Bombs!
Place bombs!
Gain a ho...
Oh!
Dude!
That sounds really good, depending on how fast they home.
I don't want to buy anything else in here.
I'm good.
Maybe the heart, but not yet.
Good night, sir!
Oh my god, that's so good!
Look at that!
I don't know what's happening, but I like it!
That has to be like... Oh, hold on.
Let me try and shoot a bunch here.
Is that what that glitched item does?
Sometimes it just...
The attack gets stuck.
Or maybe it's only when I hit something.
Yeah, maybe it's only when I hit an enemy, then there's a chance for that to occur.
Um, nine coins.
I'm just going to keep going.
What the... Oh, it's like a sipper!
Sipper voice!
Oh, okay!
They're doing lasers!
And they're spawning demon voice!
I don't know how I'm not taking any damage here.
Well, I'm somehow managing.
That's a messed up enemy.
No coins for that.
I guess I can make things free again.
Maybe I want that, actually.
That was a mistake.
I'll buy another one and save it for the next floor.
Uh-oh.
Wait, are we going into the womb here?
Is that standard procedure in these?
What the hell?
I feel like that's new.
Oh, maybe not, actually.
The last boss still seems to be the hanged man.
What is that?
Best friend, fuck that.
This looks cool.
Technology zero!
Static...
Tears?
Tears have a small beam, or tears have small beams of electricity that arc between them.
Ealing 30%... Oh my god, really?
I hope that works with this laser.
It's like chain lightning or something.
Then we have squeezy soul hearts.
Placenta a red heart.
I like that.
Give me another red heart.
Damn right.
Uh, something just fell down.
It was that heart.
Let's look for secrets.
Okay.
Then it's got to be in here.
I feel like it's only one of these two options.
Or not.
Okay.
Uh, milk or breakfast?
Oh, wait!
Should we try and dig in the greed mode?
That is a possibility.
Okay, well, we get milk.
I like it.
We can re-roll.
We'd love to find another battery.
We're definitely taking a devil deal if we are being presented with it.
That was absolutely atrocious.
What am I even doing here?
Disgusting.
Embarrassing.
I promise to do better.
You know what?
There's one downside to using the keyboard.
It's something I've noticed.
Like, if I hold up on the arrow... You can try on your own keyboard right now.
Try and hold with your middle finger on the up key.
And then try quickly switch to the down key.
It's actually really awkward.
You know, going from up to down...
It's tough on the keyboard.
I imagine that is easier on a controller.
Also, kind of throwing away all my HP.
Let's just play it safely here.
No reason to go crazy.
Nice!
16 coinos!
Maybe for the shovel, make it free.
Okay.
The rosary bead.
I do like the Bible.
And I think I want to buy a key instead.
Okay.
I'll take a key.
I don't want that shovel.
I do want to open this.
Shit!
Well, that ain't good.
Wow!
Yeah, the backstab!
Oi, oi.
Easy.
Next!
Oi, oi, oi.
Oh, I can hit the feet!
That's cool.
Yeah!
Angels!
The halo!
Speed, damage, range, health.
Ooh, that seems really good.
I'm like an angel demon now.
Checkmate atheists.
I think I'm done.
11 coins.
I am done here.
Unless I go look for a secret room.
Let's try that actually.
Maybe down here.
Nope.
It's probably inside this room here.
Okay, let's check it out.
Let's try it.
Okay.
Now I'm confused.
Is it really down here?
Can it even be down here?
Okay!
Well, there we go.
Oh man, that hurts.
That is so sad.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Going swimmingly so far, this is a fantastic warm-up run.
You can't ask for better.
I freaking love this item.
That gives me two options in here.
One of the best items.
There you go.
Cube of Meat.
I think I want that instead of this, because I have enough red hearts at this point.
I'll take this.
Yep.
Aha!
Thank you.
Now, what do we got here?
We got a white rectangle.
And Tropicamide.
Range is so huge for me that I think I should buy this no matter what.
But before I do, maybe we can make it free.
So let's just give it a little bit here before we buy it.
What's that?
Apple of Sodom.
Ah, nah.
Let's charge up this bad boy here.
Ah, that was bad.
Mistakes were made.
Wait, are they duplicating my attacks?
What just happened there?
Oh, it's me!
I wasn't good enough.
Meow!
Haha, I love doing that.
What's up, bro?
We're fully charged.
Please, dear God above, grant me onto me the free Tropicamide.
Ah, fine.
I'll purchase it with my own money.
And then we have a safety pin, even more range!
Yes!
Maybe I should have bought this just to see what it was, but, you know.
I mean, this is going fantastic.
You can't really complain.
Imagine if that immediately opened the secret as well.
Okay, fine.
We're not that lucky.
The range is out of control now.
I can play so safe.
Next!
Oh, you bastard!
Okay, no props.
I think I'm gonna...
17 coins.
Let's buy this, I want to see.
Blank card!
Card mimic.
Triggers the effect of the card held without consuming it.
Ooh!
That sounds really freaking good.
If you get a good card...
Like, imagine you get Sun, and you have this thing.
That would be pretty dope.
But, I haven't even seen a card in this run, except the one I start with, so...
I'm okay.
Yep.
Let's try and get a key.
Or save up for a key here, at least.
We can get into that treasure room.
Okay.
Oh, angels are on my side!
What is that even?
Spear of destiny!
Whoa!
Grants a spear melee weapon that deals contact damage.
The spear sometimes inflicts fear on enemies it touches.
Whoa!
I mean, that better be really good, right?
Otherwise, it's not a good idea to get into melee range.
Okay, let's get a key.
Ah, we don't have coins for it.
Yeah!
I'll take that.
Why not?
Am I really gonna not get in there?
That's crazy, bro.
Maybe there's something in here I can grab.
Oh, that one is really good.
Emergency contact?
I may actually go with that.
Yeah, this one is fantastic.
We're gonna save that for the final boss.
It does pain me to leave the treasure room behind, but, you know.
Oh, wait, this is the shop floor.
Uh-uh-uh.
Let me see here.
Stapler is really good.
Box of friends.
Hey, that's funny.
That's the one that Yulith has.
Large sit.
I think we just start.
We get going.
That range, though...
Pop your little head up.
Wait, what?
Dude!
These guys have no chill.
Man, they fucking nailed the combat in this game.
Like...
Just the sheer amount of things you can encounter and...
how different the game feels like every single time you play, you know?
It's quite something.
Ah, they exploded!
Let's just play it safe and always keep it a distance here.
I think that's wise.
Like that.
No reason to be risky.
Okay, here we go.
Wish me luck.
Nice!
Need more money.
I can buy a key, though.
Buy a key?
Oh, wait, we don't have a treasure room here, so let's not do that.
Hey!
Okay.
Thought I saw blue in here.
I'm gonna bomb this.
Wait, did I already bomb that?
Fuck.
I may have bombed that already.
I don't recall.
I think right here.
Too bad.
Moving on!
It's Daddy Long Legs.
And boy, his legs are long.
Dude, that glitch to attack just now murdered this guy.
Fifteen coins, exactly.
It's gotta be the stapler.
It's just so much damage.
Like, you can't go wrong with that.
Ooh.
Ooh, ooh, man, I want that so bad.
Holy shit.
Okay, here we go.
Oh!
There's a lot!
Battle of the lasers.
We got devil.
Ladies and gentlemen, what's it gonna be?
A knife?
Sacrificial altar, consumed to sacrifice up to two familiars, so I have one.
For each familiar sacrifice, one random devil room pedestal item is spawned.
I think I'm gonna use this.
Not even kidding.
Ultimate play!
The ultimate!
I cannot be stopped.
I have the infinite range.
Now I just need bombs and keys.
And money.
I need all of it, actually.
I'm getting low on HP, though.
Gotta be careful here.
Yeah.
Oh, look, 11 out of 10 coins now.
Huh.
We're on the last floor.
Ultra greed.
I guess on this floor it doesn't make sense to bring the coupon.
That was a misplay, and I did it purposefully to bait you.
To bait your rage.
It was not unintentional.
Oh, that's a bit late for that, but I'll take it.
Okay, come on.
Ultra greed.
I'm gonna blow your ass up.
We're gonna play Space Invaders.
Kinda.
Oh, I can destroy the coins!
Sick.
Oh, I'm losing a lot of HP here.
Come on.
I've got...
Okay, my damage is not that great.
It's good, but, you know, it's not unbelievably good.
Oh, goodness gracious!
Man, that Brimstone is just out here murdering things.
Oh, wait, did I heal him?
What happened?
Oh, I see.
Those coins are bad.
You cannot destroy those.
That's a bad idea.
Kill these guys.
Wait, these are the normal coins.
We got them.
There it is.
Okay, wait a minute.
I think I'm actually fucking this up, guys.
I think the whole point is to save up money for this machine.
I just realized, the whole shtick with this game mode is that you have to balance what you buy versus what you end up putting in at the end.
Now, I don't know what I'm gonna get if I put things in at the end, but I think I just realized that is what I need to do.
And, yeah, well, we did it!
Kinda.
Cheers.
Okay.
It's the same one, right?
Nothing different about this?
Yeah.
It's the same.
Skip it.
Skipity-doo, toilet, or whatever people say.
We are gonna go ahead and do a challenge now.
Yeah.
Man, the solar system is calling.
I hear you, but I think I have to do this in order.
We gotta try this one again.
Darkness falls.
I wanna do challenges.
Uh, we have a knife that is rotating.
Oh, yeah, right!
Brace a blade.
I remember this now.
Dark matter.
Pentagram.
Sacrificial dagger.
Right.
Okay.
Hold on, someone's calling me.
Someone was at my door, and they were like, uh...
What's up, son?
Can you let me in?
And I'm like, I think you got the wrong door here.
I was like, oh, shit, my son is named Oliver.
I can't believe it.
Uh, do you mind letting me in?
So I went to the door, I was like, what's up, mom?
And then we laughed about it.
That was kind of funny.
So apparently, there's another one named Oliver in my building.
Let's just go ahead and kill these birds.
No, uh, flies.
Ah, got you with the rage bait!
Oh, no!
Oh, it wasn't even a rage bait.
I'm gonna stop saying that word now, actually.
I'm getting tired of this.
Whoa, actually, why am I doing this?
I almost damaged myself twice there.
For no reason.
Oh, I think the knife just murdered him!
He insta-died to that.
Dude, the knife?
Yo, the knife is actually kind of good.
Let's try and kill him with the knife.
Okay, the knife blocked something there.
Yeah, slice him up!
Yeah!
I'm the murderer in the alleyway.
It's a real song.
Gimme.
Oh, I see this.
I see it.
My eagle eyes have spotted the secret rock.
These are fierce.
Man, this person here is doing a lot of damage.
Oh, my eagle eye has spotted another potential subject.
Okay, this is going really well.
Dude, today is blessed in Isaac.
Loving it!
Fantastic run so far.
Also, look at the way the light shafts are coming in from the top.
I think that means there's a higher chance of getting the angel stuff.
Even though the UI is at 0%.
There's some kind of indicator about angel stuff.
Maybe not the angel room, but something angel related.
Oh, geez!
Fuck me, Jackie!
What the hell?
Dude!
Oh!
Jackie just jumped up on the table, bumped into my keyboard, and I got such a fright because for a second I'm not even kidding.
I thought the mama...
Well, she's not my mom, but the person who thought I was her son jumped on my table and I don't know why my mind thought that, but because I just mentioned it, you know, I was like, is she now behind me?
It was... Oh, man.
That just messed with me.
Whoo!
Rough.
Man, oh, man.
Okay, you're a feared now.
Oh, and there's creep on the floor.
Careful.
Careful now.
Okay, okay, okay.
One of them's gonna charge any...
Moment out!
Yeah, okay.
Wait, I wonder if these bosses are predetermined.
Call me crazy, but didn't we get this boss last time I played this character?
And didn't I get supper as well?
Unless I'm totally just hallucinating like an LLM right now.
Maybe I am, actually.
Oh, well, we're doing fantastic in the health department.
We actually can't lose.
Let me guess, it's the sun.
Okay, that's good too.
I was just trying to project my luck based on previous events, you know.
Extrapolate.
Wait, do I want anything?
What is that?
Wait, that's the third type of battery in this game.
Well, there's nothing I really want.
I'm good.
Definitely stepping in here, though.
Would you look at that?
It was totally worth it.
Actually, hold on, ten coins?
Was there anything I wanted to buy?
Or do I save the money?
The ultimate question.
I could buy this hard, but nah.
Save it.
We're going to purchase the 15 coin in the next floor.
Or on the next floor.
My work here is done.
That's a lot of floors, though.
I could also cut myself here, you know, gain some more damage.
That is the whole point of this character.
I got to keep that in mind.
But honestly, so far I don't need to.
But this is going well.
Come here.
I want to blow that up.
Much better.
Kill spiders first and then we go on the guy.
These guys are too irregular.
Oh my goodness.
The knife once again saved me.
Very nice.
Dude, I think I'm actually legitimately getting a lot better at the game.
Because I haven't played this game for like three days.
Is it?
Or maybe four?
And I feel like I'm already, you know, already into it and I'm doing so well.
It's a great indicator.
Yeah!
Man.
Oh, that's not good.
You know what?
Get stomped on.
Are you there?
Oh, the 90 degree turn was made for that moment.
Delighted over him.
Always fast.
Do not get hit by the laser.
What is this guy?
Oh, he's feared.
I stepped on the freaking creep.
I feel like I should damage the small guy instead.
Like I'm, this is horrible.
Oh, but I can't.
Let's chill over here.
More breakfast.
Why not?
And a devil deal.
Too spooky.
And death list.
I like that one.
This is such a fun item.
I'm taking both.
This is why we get the red hearts.
People.
Listen up.
Take notes.
I should also take notes, actually.
I should take more notes.
But I haven't encountered anything noteworthy yet, I guess.
Treasure room shall be searched for.
Whoa, that was close.
Let's wait.
Oh, no.
What?
Get in.
Wow.
That was scary.
Oh, the more options one is so good.
We have to come back for that.
Wait, there's no more rooms.
Oh.
This way.
Yeah, kill them in order.
Oh, no, the diagonal shots are gonna fuck me.
Okay, okay.
Not that guy, not that guy.
Okay, we'll kill this guy then.
The little guy.
Yes.
Amazing.
We got the money.
Get in.
Push.
Dude, this room is one of the hardest rooms I've ever seen in the game so far.
That is so hard to dodge.
Okay.
Come here.
Just take it slow now.
No reason to go nuts.
Why did I enter?
That was a mistake.
Actually, maybe not.
Become a whore.
Maybe blow something up.
Okay.
Not too shabby.
Let's get back.
I don't know if I should take these hearts or should I stay in horror mode?
I'm gonna stay in horror mode.
I just saw a tinted rock.
I got no bombs.
I didn't mean to pick that up.
It was total, you know, impulse.
Base instincts.
But I can't just remove it if I want to.
Or I go in here and remove it like that, huh?
Calculated.
Oh, I thought it was gonna blow this up for me.
That's too bad.
Oh wait, no, never mind.
That damages my blue hearts.
Of course.
Yeah.
True.
Oh well.
The idea was good.
I should kill them in order.
I think I already messed it up, actually.
We got a bomb now?
Ooh, two bombs.
You know what that means?
Ah, then I have to walk through that again, Adam.
Maybe not worth it.
Yeah, I think I'm good.
Did I just mess it up again?
I forgot to look for the kill order.
Okay, let's not mess it up now.
You.
Shit.
Did I mess it up?
No, I didn't.
This guy needs to come over here?
No, he died.
Okay, new rule.
We only do the kill order when there's an easy room.
Otherwise, we're just going to completely disregard it.
That's the new rule, and we're going to follow it.
There's having coins already.
This one looks easy.
Actually, I'm kidding.
It's impossible.
We disregard the kill order.
We execute order 66.
Whoa.
I'm glad they got feared.
I wonder if they get feared because of the knife.
They're like, ooh, he has a knife.
Let's back up.
Point me.
Oh, we turned it black in here.
I wonder what that actually does.
Or if it's just a visual effect.
Dreamcatcher, Grant's Soulheart.
I mean, that one is a must for me.
And look at that, we see this card now.
Oh, but, oh.
For some reason, I thought in Greek mode, the stuff you found was not saved, you know?
Wait, let me think.
Or maybe that was challenge.
I'm not sure.
It's one of them, at least.
Paralysis?
No, thanks.
I'm good.
Just getting a Soulheart every floor is massive.
No, don't kill him.
Yeah, get away from me.
Okay, then we kill this guy.
Huge!
That is massive.
Six bombs.
I could look for secrets.
In fact, I'm pretty sure there's a secret here.
Look, there's even a little... it's gotta be.
Okay.
Well, I got you baited.
So it's not down here.
Maybe it's in the next room.
Like, right here, you know?
I'm actually gonna do it from this side.
Yep.
There it is.
What the heck is that?
Looks like some kind of Microsoft app.
Missing numbers, syntax error.
We lost range?
No.
Tears?
Shot speed but gained luck.
Reroll's Isaac stats and all collected.
Oh...
This reroll effect triggers again at the start.
Oh, what did I just do?
Oh, no.
Pentagram.
Wait, no, no, no.
Hold on, what?
Read it again.
Oh, and all collected items.
So the items you start with stay.
I see.
Okay.
So wait, that's like...
It just changed again.
Or maybe it's just because I paused the game technically?
By opening the menu?
Hmm...
Dude, so far so good with the kill order?
Kill him!
This guy...
No!
The fucking 90 degree!
You know what?
You're outta here!
Thanks.
Much better.
I can't believe I got sabotaged like that.
Yep.
Moving on.
So this guy, I don't remember what he does.
Okay, that one.
Uh... Okay, bottom guy first!
Ah, I'm actually gonna die!
I really shouldn't just try and kill them in the right order.
Like, it's bad.
It's a... No!
Kill him!
Oh, thank God.
Book of Belial.
You know what?
Maybe I should take that.
We get a blue heart now, though.
And we can also see what's coming up.
Let's see.
What do we get?
It is?
Ah, but wait, it was rerolled!
Huh?
Why did we lose our... Wait a minute.
Something's going on right here.
No, not the blue heart hole!
Oh, man, this is rough!
Let's just spend our days in the arcade.
I never wanna leave.
Uh... Here, I have a coin.
Okay.
Give me more.
What up?
Here.
Come on, guys, please.
I'm in dire stra- Oh, what up?
I looked at my bombs.
I fucking thought I had seven keys.
Oh, shit!
Well, that was nice.
Hey, not bad!
Let's go blow some shit up.
Very nice.
Okay.
My damage is out of control, though.
This is the one upside right now.
God.
Oof.
Strength.
Two of clubs.
Ooh, that's nice.
I'll take that.
Oh, God.
Blow them up.
Yeah, good, good, good.
Okay.
Actually, I'm gonna go back, because I saw a shop.
Play safe.
Phew.
Nice!
That is actually so important.
No, it's not a real shop!
I see another tinted rock.
Come on, then.
Jump over here.
Ooh.
Man, oh, man.
Oh, shit!
I didn't even see that.
Mistakes.
I mean, we can still do this.
We just gotta focus here.
This is okay.
We're not lost yet.
Well, of course, it depends on the random items we're gonna get at the start of each floor!
That is such a crazy frickin' item to start with.
I mean, we could get lucky.
Maybe we get brimstone, imagine.
I choose to believe in the luck.
Now we go back, because we had a key.
I needed that for something.
It was a chest, right?
Down here?
Yep.
Ooh, nice!
Stable that eye.
More damage is good.
Glass cannon, at least, is something we can go for now.
We are basically as Hazel without the flying and the laser.
And name.
Thank you.
Should I go for it?
Not yet.
This guy throws bombs.
I think.
Getting good keys.
I'm 32 coins.
I really wanna go donate something.
Or buy something.
The left hand.
You know.
Nah.
I was about to say, maybe it's a good idea, because we don't have that many keys.
But I do like my current trinket very much.
I'm surprised I dealt with this room so nicely.
I smell a secret.
I'm never wrong.
Okay.
See you later.
Ooh, wait a minute then.
See, it would be a waste to use a bomb there.
So I'm taking the long way.
What?
Boyoyoyo!
Fuck!
We're definitely belialing against that boss.
The belial will be biblical.
Here we go.
Wish me luck against the carrion queen.
Boink!
Oh no, this one's tough.
But I have good damage.
Just DPS'n down, man.
Kill him.
He's bleeding.
The creep is not blinking!
That's good!
Fucka!
Watch out!
Unpredictable, holy...
I can't hit him!
Wow!
I can't believe I did that!
Aw, this is the worst item though.
We can't go in there, unfortunately.
Actually, we can.
We have a black heart now.
Should I?
Okay.
Cursed eye.
Chart shot that fires up to five tears in a burst.
Yeah, no thanks.
That sounds like a bad idea.
Matchstick.
I think we just move on.
Get outta here.
Okay.
What's the status?
Seven damage.
What's the damage?
Lipstick.
Seven seals.
Grants a wandering harbinger familiar that spawns locusts.
Okay.
It shifts form every ten seconds.
Alright.
I've mined.
Got it.
Well, can we re-roll the missing number at some point?
Momsk... Ooh, okay.
Lord of the Pit.
We fly!
No shit!
Okay.
Jesus juice.
And this is all the same.
Voodoo head.
Improved layouts and rewards within curse rooms.
Also causes one coin to spawn.
I think I get it.
Nice.
Well.
Let's just roll with it.
Man, my tears are really slow, though.
That's actually really bad.
Oh, this is painful!
Tears and shot speed is down the shitter right now.
Oh, no.
I hate it.
Dude, what are those white flies?
Fuck me!
Oh, wait.
They're with me.
Why did they damage me?
Geobro!
Kill it!
I think I'm dead.
Oh, wait.
I fly.
I can fly now.
Strength.
Heels.
But we need some, well, extra hearts for that.
Yikes!
How did I not take damage?
That was scary.
Flying is amazing.
Oh, yeah.
I can fly.
You know what?
I think we have to do this.
I don't know what that is, but I'm taking it!
I feel cozy now.
I can also shoot in case I need to boop.
There should be no need for the shoot here.
Wait, I have a shit-ton of hearts?
Suddenly?
Huh?
Don't question it.
Just go with it.
What the heck?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Dude, I am fucking rich with hearts, baby!
Rich with hearts.
I can't lose.
I'm actually on top of the fucking world right now.
Yep, yep, yep.
Kill him.
Kill him!
Get out of there.
I can't lose.
Oh, my God, I would get the insane-o key.
Insane-o?
Oh, wait, this is my friend.
It's my friend.
Everything's fine.
We are actually just winning.
We can't lose this.
This is insanity.
Holy shit.
Give me the secrets to the...
Wait a minute.
No, this way.
Go down here.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna mess you up.
I can't lose!
Doesn't matter if I have slow bullets.
Doesn't matter at all.
Come on, then.
No!
Oh, yeah.
Almost had me there.
Not quite.
This will be remembered as the day you almost caught Eulith.
Oh, wait, we're not Eulith.
We are Babylon Woman.
Got her name.
No!
They shoot through thingies!
For some reason, I'm like, I'm safe behind this rock over here.
Nope.
I'm not safe against the laser.
Lasers are dangerous beings.
What?
Dude, I need to find a shop.
Right now.
Okay.
Nope.
This is a secret right here.
Yep, always right.
Dude, I'm so excited to see what we're gonna get on the next floor.
Huh?
I'm lazy, so I'm gonna do this.
That was totally unnecessary, but I did it anyway.
Gimme.
Okay, the shop's gonna be in the south, then.
There's just no other explanation.
Come on.
Wait, uh, hold on, everything is on sale?
Oh yeah, steam sale, right.
Uh, right.
Uh, potato peeler consumes a red heart container to grant a permanent cube of meat.
Well, I don't have any red ones.
I have this, though.
Definitely buying that.
Also, definitely taking pills.
Fuck.
I guess it doesn't matter.
Everything's gonna be rerolled anyway.
So wait, does any item I pick up...
Oh, wait a minute, actually.
If I...
Dude, I need to think about it like this.
Any active or any, like, item I pick up is gonna be another item potential reroll.
So I should actually just be picking up everything.
The more, the better.
Because items are rarely bad.
They're always good, right?
Well, not always, but almost always.
This is the strategy.
We pick up everything.
We buy everything.
Oh, he's with me.
Time for the boss.
I should have probably saved the shoot for the boss.
Ah, it's okay.
Go for it.
Monstro?
That's smite.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Guys, I'm throwing it.
On purpose!
I'm doing it on purpose.
This entire stream was scripted, by the way, by one of my interns.
He came up with the idea of, you know, first having that greed run where I just didn't have any money again.
That was the first stage, you know?
The second stage was, let's do a challenge.
I can't even say that with a straight face.
That is just too funny.
Okay, we got him.
We got him.
What?
Fuck this matchbook.
Actually, I love it.
We get a black card.
Everything going according to scripts.
I wish I was not lying.
I mean, I wish I was lying.
Oh, my God.
This is...
Let's see what we got here.
Eleven damage.
Money.
Very nice.
Crackjacks.
Shoot the loop.
We got a catanine tail.
Ceremonial ropes.
Except this is not actually going to help me very much.
Piggybank.
BFFs.
Doubles the damage of familiars.
Okay.
Hey, nice.
Little horn.
Fire a void.
Something with bighorn's hand.
That's the thing that comes out of the ground.
Instantly kills normal guys.
Spoonbox.
Okay, got it.
The situation has been analyzed, scrutinized, and...
I will now act upon the information.
You'll see what I mean.
I cannot lose any HP.
Thank God I don't have a shitty tier now.
I'm shooting fast again.
Oh, wait, I'm not flying.
We're not flying anymore.
Alert, alert.
Keep it in mind.
This is big.
Do not think you can fly.
Don't go jump off any houses now.
Oh, that's a good one.
I'm taking that.
Good.
Solid.
Let's see here.
That's just another item for the item bank.
Money equals power on this floor.
Ah, wait, it doesn't reveal secret rooms.
It's only those special ones.
True.
Man, that hand is...
Not bad.
Oi!
This guy juked me, actually.
You see the way he turned around there?
I'm playing it safe here.
Also, I'm super fast on this floor.
Oh, no, oh, no.
Ah, we're fine.
Oi!
Oh, the shop.
Even though money equals power, we gotta buy.
We're buying this.
Ah, mom's bracelet.
Grab and pick up a rock.
Nah.
See, that's not... that's an active, so it doesn't really matter.
Don't care about that.
We're probably not gonna have money equals power on the next floor, right?
So, may as well spend some money on things.
On a card, perhaps.
The stars!
Isn't that the one with the secret room?
Ah, maybe not.
I'm not sure where that took me.
Oh, I'm not stepping.
Not in this outfit.
I'm tempted to shoot here.
Wait, wow, the hand took the mask.
You didn't need to go through the heart first.
That's a cool interaction.
Massively done.
Oh, massive, that is so good.
Muchly needed.
That's fine.
As long as we're on one heart, right?
That's the thing.
Oh, wait, I'm throwing, I'm throwing.
This isn't part of the script.
The script to it says Oliver wins now.
We need to follow it.
To the letter.
Shit.
Come on.
No!
Actually, we're chilling.
Just gotta be careful for the hand.
It's not going well.
Oh, what the...
Dude, I'm in trouble.
If that hand comes down, I'm dead.
Okay, thank God.
Oi!
Kill him, kill him, kill him, kill him.
Where's the hand?
There it is.
Good damage, good damage.
Keep moving, keep moving.
Keep moving!
Yeah, dude, yes!
Oh, beautiful.
Mr. Dolly, tears, whatever.
Black hearts.
Ah, that's fine too.
That's fine too.
Oh!
Oh, I thought it was brimstone.
See ya!
See ya, I'm leaving.
I'm getting the hell out of there.
Let's see what we get.
I did not see those red fires.
Like, what I mean is, I didn't even pay attention to it, you know?
Okay.
X-9?
Let's see here.
Dead cat?
Okay.
Dinner.
Charter glass.
The search.
Glass eye.
Options.
Dreamcatcher.
Mom's key.
Blue.
Oh, nice!
Bogobombs.
Ghost baby.
Dark matter.
Pentagram.
I mean, it's not that good.
It's good!
It's good.
It's very good.
Oh yeah, baby.
What the?
Why there's so many items in that chest?
Oh, man.
We have become a sizzle!
Time is on my side.
Two for one.
Remember, I do not fly.
I almost wanted to walk into the creek there.
Dude, this is great.
But remember, it's only for one floor.
Let's not get overexcited.
Oh, okay.
That's actually pretty nice.
Joker.
Why not?
Dry baby.
Following familiar the block.
Yeah?
Then why not?
And then we take this one, too.
Grant's flight and Leviathan three out of three now.
What does that mean again?
Leviathan?
Maybe just...
I'm not sure.
What that means.
In any case, we are rolling right now.
Holy.
I can't lose.
Even this guy can't stop me.
I'm also rich, by the way.
I'm successful.
I'm rich.
I'm handsome.
Precharge.
I wonder what's best.
My normal attack or the Shoop?
I think the Shoop is better still.
But I'm not sure.
Eh, no thanks.
I've used that too much in the past and it was never good.
Well, that was not good.
Oh, you're still alive.
Minus one range?
I mean, no.
No, thanks.
Actually, it doesn't matter.
Give me.
What are you gonna do about it?
That was the scripted two out of three rage baits on this floor.
There's one more coming up, guys.
I can't reveal when, but it's coming.
What's that?
Amnesia.
Oh, no!
Wait, another range down?
Why not?
I can't lose.
I take that.
Can't make it too easy now, right?
Give me that.
Wait, boss is here.
You know what?
I think it's good.
Okay, that did that much damage.
I think it's a little bit better than my normal attack, but it's not a lot.
You know, it's slightly.
Bar of soap or whatever this is.
White pony flight and holy death?
Hold on.
Dash across the screen, spawning a trail of damaging light beams.
Isaac is invulnerable and deals contact damage.
Grants flight while held.
Increases speed to 1.5 while held.
There's speed status below that.
What was the thing about holy death?
Maybe something happens if I die on that thing.
Oh, yeah, this one we already robbed.
Um, I guess it's gonna be changed out anyway.
Just move on.
Let's see.
This is all the same.
Screw.
I have the occult.
Ooh.
Nice.
But wait, there's no more shops.
Hold on.
There we go.
That was uncomfortable.
Sharp block using an uncharged item.
Uncharged item.
Uh, whatever.
Nice.
But we're amnesiaed up.
That's bad.
Black card is good.
Immunity to floor curses.
That's good.
Wait, I'm not immune to floor curses.
That's a lie.
I have a curse on.
What the frick?
The mark.
Placenta.
Bloodshot eye.
Binky.
Little baggy.
Squeezy white.
Oh!
Well, right, of course, it's an active.
Missing page two.
Goat head.
Oh, wait, these are very similar looking.
Ouija board.
Okay.
I can't see shit, though.
I don't know where I am.
Come here.
Wait, am I...
Oh, wait, I'm still flying!
Why am I still flying?
Grant's flight?
This is... oh, wait.
Grant's flight while held?
Not while active?
Did I get that right?
Hold on.
Wait, can I...
How was it again?
I hold it double-click.
Spam.
Control.
I forgot how to drop the active.
It's okay.
I think it's actually what's doing this.
Yeah, look, I'm flying on the horse.
It's gotta be, right?
I have a little horsey.
I'm like Harry Potter.
Okay.
Let's check for suspicious rocks.
This one is...
Suspicious!
No.
I was so sure that one was sus.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna take damage from that.
No.
See, why is there no description on that?
I think that's a bug.
Because when I go in here, it shows me.
Never mind.
What?
Why doesn't it show me?
So maybe it's not a bug.
Nice.
Dude, I'm going straight for the boss.
I feel like my setup is good here.
I have a good chance.
Actually, I just lost some HP.
That's bad.
I'll fucking do it again.
No, I won't.
I won't.
Enough is enough.
Uh-oh!
Oh, no.
We're gonna die.
We don't have nine lives anymore.
This one, though, for sure, no?
Oh, no.
Die!
Oh, man.
How are we gonna sub...?
Hello.
Shit!
Okay.
Wait, umbilical?
Where?
Oh, there.
When entering a room with half a red heart or less, gain a little Steven familiar.
I mean, that's... that's... good.
Yeah.
But now my range is utterly disgusting.
It's not that bad, actually.
One hit and I'm down.
This needs to be precision gaming.
There's no other way to put it.
I need an arcade.
And secrets.
No frickin' way.
Paperclip.
I don't care.
No, give me blue hearts or black hearts.
That's the boss.
Oh, with half an HP?
I can't do it.
I'm gonna die.
But I think if I go back, I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna have to try this.
Remind me the active here.
He's invulnerable.
Dashes across the screen.
Invulnerable.
But how long does it last?
Oh, man.
Ooh.
We're gonna try it.
Put down some creep along the eyes that are gonna spawn.
Wish me luck.
I need it.
Like, this...
It's not even skill at this point.
This is...
I don't understand how the active worked.
I fucked myself because I didn't know what was going on.
I thought I could go to, like, horizontally across the screen.
Shit.
Man.
I haven't fucking won a challenge in ten years.
Okay.
It's time for a speedrun.
I have decided we're gonna do an assasal ultimate speedrun now.
We're gonna beat the timer.
Fuck!
I didn't mean to do this.
I didn't mean to go to greed!
I mean, we can do another greed, I guess.
This time we're gonna save up money.
This is the big change we're gonna make.
We're gonna get rich and save up a lot of money.
This is the plan.
Ah, let's see here.
Oh, that one is gonna pay off in the long run for sure.
What else do I want?
Yeah, that's fine.
Nice that the keys are on sale.
Ah, no way!
I didn't even see the fucking spike.
I thought it disappeared, like, after you click on it once.
Oh, cancelled my attack!
Oh, yo-yo.
Nice!
It's not a good start here.
Focus up.
Kill the small guys.
Okay, well, that was pretty good.
18 coins.
Now, plus one health.
I think we gotta take that.
It's a must.
Then we grab a key.
Open this door.
Oh, wait, is that...
Oh, man, I hate that item.
I don't even want it.
I need coins.
No, thanks.
It's a duke!
The duke is so easy to kill as Azazel.
Whoopsie.
One more coin and I have 15.
Oh, I really want to buy one of these.
Especially the pentagram.
Maybe there's a coin in that flame.
This feels so bad.
I may have to go in here and spend a black card on this.
No, actually, hold on.
We're saving money anyway.
Ah, wait, we have a fool!
We're chilling.
Ex-lax.
Nice!
Not bad.
Going bombs at me.
We got a devil room.
Wait,
two blue hearts and a red?
I have two black hearts.
I think this will kill me if I take it.
Makes tears increasing.
Like, what is this even?
Why do I want to sacrifice a whole heart for that?
It's not that good.
I feel like it's not great at all.
Well, okay, I'm going to spend some money here.
We're going to buy this one.
Yep.
We're going to start saving money a little later in the run.
This is the plan.
In the beginning, we get crucial items.
And then it's saving up time.
You'll see.
Maybe when we reach halfway point, you know, then we start saving.
Depending on how powerful we are.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Except that's terrible.
Three red hearts.
Yikes.
Cat on nine tails.
This one's very cheap.
But it's not very good for me.
This guy wants bombs.
He's not getting it.
I hate when I accidentally cancelled my own attack.
Kind of want to see if there's a timer in green mode.
In the loading screen.
Let's try and pay attention next time.
18 coins.
A lot of damage and shot speed, I mean.
I think this is just solid.
It's a solid item to buy.
Yep.
Happy with that.
But now we're going to need a key, though.
Wait, can I actually get coins from these poops that he's spawning?
Is this infinite money glitch?
Let me check.
Keep pooping, son.
Maybe.
I don't think so.
I mean, we could just be unlucky.
Okay, 12 coins.
We buy a key here.
Be something really good.
That's a new one.
Soy milk.
Damage down and tears way up.
Whoa.
Infinite puke.
But goodbye damage.
I don't know if this is good.
We'll have to see.
I think it's not good.
Oh, no.
We definitely need to get a damage up now.
Somehow.
Actually, I could blow myself in here.
No, I can't.
That's not...
Yes, it is worth it.
Blow that up.
We get two bombs, right?
We can do the same here.
Those.
We can actually look for a secret now.
Not there.
Let's try this.
Yeah, I don't know if I like it.
I mean, it's cool, but...
It's too risky.
Like, I'm gonna take too much damage with this, you know?
The longer it takes to kill an enemy, the more chances of getting hit.
Oh, my God.
Devil.
Multidimensional baby and... false PhD.
I mean, that's a black heart.
Converter red to a black?
It's not... too bad.
Right?
It's not too bad.
But why would I want to do it, though?
Converter most gold pill effects into bad?
Maybe this one, though.
Friendly tears that pass through it are doubled and gain increased damage and shot speed.
Now, that could be nice in combination with my current setup here.
If you angle it right, let's try it.
This may have been a massive mistake, but look at this.
Oh, no, it's hard to do.
He's wobbling all over the place.
I thought he would be more stable.
Shit.
I may have fucked up here.
I'm taking the key.
Moving on.
Okay, so on next floor, we're going to start saving money.
Unless we just haven't found any damage.
Wait, I need to go down here first.
What is that?
Raw liver.
Hey!
Sick!
Plus two health!
That is one of the best items in the game.
Incredible.
Trick or treat!
We gained tears.
Can't have to fire a razor blade that deals four...
Spawn it!
It's not every time I click, right?
Come on.
Is that it?
No, that's not familiar.
Oh, man, it may not work with my laser.
That's too bad.
Now, this thing up here could spawn on some nice hearts if we get the money.
More range?
It's actually not a bad idea.
That's only five cents.
I can get it now.
And then some.
Then again, damage.
It's only .28.
Wait, why is it... I feel like the stapler is randomized?
I definitely have seen the stapler give two point something damage at one point.
But yeah, I'll take this.
Oh, something spawned.
Ringworm.
No, thanks.
I'm just happy it's not lasers.
We're like the angel version of Azazel.
With the light tears, you know, light laser.
It's not that bad.
It's just a little slow.
But I do prefer the hit and run strategies of not the continuous laser.
I feel like it's more safe.
Like the boss is going to be tough to beat with this, I think.
20 coins.
We're saving from the next floor and onward.
Man, I'm actually...
If we save too much and don't buy items, we're also going to be underpowered, right?
What's that?
I mean, that's not going to matter for me.
I think I'll buy this heart.
Yeah, I'll take this heart.
And I'm going to donate some to this thing.
Wait, I can keep buying here.
Two red hearts.
That's cool.
Let's do this one and then move on.
Oh, man.
I'm trying to align my baby here.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Oi, oi, oi.
15 coins.
We're going to move on and see what we get in the next floor.
And if there's something worth buying, like something really good, we're going to do it.
If not, we're going to start saving.
This is the plan.
The problem is we just don't have any damage.
It's going to be rough.
Range is good.
Yeah, actually, range is good.
Wait,
did I see an X?
Doesn't it look like there's an X on this rock right here?
Actually, no, this is the same as that one.
This one, though, looks like there's an X on it.
I think I may have been right.
But one red heart is not very cool.
Very underwhelming.
No.
Damage and random rune or soul stone.
Is it worth?
One more health is actually not bad either.
I think this may be worth it.
At least some sustain, you know.
We can heal up with the lovers.
I think I'm going to buy this.
Wait, what did we spawn?
Placenta, oh my God.
We're saving money now.
No more.
This is the setup we're going to go with.
It's not great.
But it is what it is.
It's kind of cool the way the attack is sort of rotating.
Switch directions, it looks nice.
Amplified damage, baby.
It's really good against these guys.
Look at that, that's beautiful.
I also need a key.
I think we should buy one key.
It's on sale as well.
Poledactily.
I was holding two cards, pills or runes.
Dropped one random card, I like it.
Nice, dude!
Incredible!
Now I feel like I should buy even more.
Nah, we're totally chilling now.
We're saving.
Nah, I stepped on the freaking X thingy.
Oh, that's a weird attack.
Whoa!
What the...
Okay.
Not too shabby, keep going.
Yeah, this guy has a lot of HP.
Did you see the amplification there?
It's nice, it feels really good when you do it.
Not bad, not bad at all, baby.
25 coins?
I could, you know what, we could reroll a little bit.
Just in case there's like an insane item.
Rotten meat.
Cube of meat.
Nah, okay, this was waste.
Shit.
Not worth it.
Oh no, not the eye.
I hate those eyes!
Man, they keep damaging me!
Wait, it lifts?
Dude, you can kind of make a diagonal attack here if you...
I just realized you can do that!
Look at that!
That's kind of sick.
Hey, that's cool.
Okay.
What do we got here?
I mean, we're saving money, right?
And we need damage?
All we're doing now is saving money.
This is worth it.
Money equals power.
This is the play.
I forgot to destroy the fires in there.
Mistake.
Okay, we can also buy that one.
Oh, let's buy a couple more.
It's going to be worth it.
That's it.
No more spending.
We're done spending.
That's it.
No more spending.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Hold on now.
We could go back.
Oi!
A door is opened.
Somewhere in greed mode as well.
Wait a minute.
No, leave it.
Or...
One more.
It's got to be worth it.
Let's go.
Okay, only saving now.
Unless we get like brimstone or some bullshit like that, right?
Then we take it.
Oh, and maybe we buy a key as well.
That's the only thing.
Increases...
Yeah.
Well, that's horrible.
That's not ideal.
I was really hoping damage would be one of the...
stats that I got more of.
I'm glad I didn't lose any damage, though.
Like, it was kind of neutral.
That's a horrible item.
That's a decent item.
This one is an unknown item.
But we're not buying.
It's only good gameplay now, and it's playing it safe.
Oh no, the Sipper Dudes.
What's the other one?
One there too?
Oh, he's up there.
He's up there.
Oh, okay.
Okay, then.
I know how it feels like to be shot with a laser.
Yikes, that hurt.
Take him out.
The diagonal laser is...
so good.
I need to use it more.
Oh no, he is.
I feel like most enemies have trouble dealing with a diagonal attack from me.
Good.
I don't know what these guys are.
I'm scared.
Oh, they got whips.
Don't you know you're fighting a Saizel?
Okay, we could buy this one for science.
No, no.
Money equals power.
We keep it.
We keep the money.
Except we get a key, though.
A key is good.
Tears become a charge attack?
Wait.
I don't think I should pick this up.
This is actually bad for me.
Uh-oh.
I think that's going to overwrite what I have, and it's going to make me turn into a shitty person.
I'm not going to do it.
Not doing it.
I will buy...
No, I'm not going to buy anything.
We're saving money.
Die.
I mean, we're not doing that much damage right now.
Oh, shit.
Whoa!
How do you dodge that?
I guess they're in that range.
Whoa.
Oi, oi, oi, oi!
This guy is insane!
Dude, I deal no damage at all.
I'm scared.
We're losing all the HP.
We may have to buy something.
We may have to get the magic scab.
Get some luck.
We can also...
Oh, we could buy a bunch of these hearts if we wanted to.
I'm going to check this out.
What?
Missing page two?
That's a good one.
Guppy's color...
Ooh.
I...
I mean, I'm going to exchange two red hearts...
for two black hearts, if you think about it.
Right?
No, three black hearts.
Oh, we're doing it.
I have convinced myself...
that this purchase was justified.
Wonderful.
Absolutely wonderful.
Now, my damage is kind of shit, though.
We're at 2.6.
I am kind of tempted to try that item in the treasure room.
It could break the run, but...
it could also make the run, depending on exactly what's happening.
I feel like with this range, though...
Okay, hold on a minute.
I can't lose HP now.
I simply can't.
Oh my god.
Cool.
No, I got hit!
Oh, ah, wait, we already went in there.
We already went in there.
It's okay.
Okay, 41 coins.
I think I'm going to have to take...
a magic scab here.
Or I...
No, actually, I could take this.
Let's take two of these.
Let me see this again.
Tears become a chart.
Isaac spits a mouthful of shots in a cone shape.
This could turn my tears into a cone.
Everything about it.
I'm going to try it.
Okay!
We like it.
We like...
We like the stock.
Oh, that is...
Oh, it's randomized.
Yo!
Look at that!
Okay!
I think we're back.
Definitely.
Nice.
And now we save.
I know I keep saying that, but for reals this time.
Absolutely no spending money.
I'm not even going to go in the shop and look at all the items.
Because there's nothing good in there anyways, right?
We don't care.
Time
to start the fights.
Can I, like, stack them?
And then deal...
Dude, this is messed up!
I can't see anything on my screen.
This may be bad.
It's going to be easier to align the stuff with my...
with my multi-dimensional baby, though.
Meow, meow, meow.
Look at this shit.
Yeah, you like that?
I mean, that is...
This is actually crazy.
No!
Not like that.
Get him, get him, get him.
Like, I can't see anything on my screen.
This is a problem.
I can't see the fucking tiles!
Oh, no.
Yeah, I can't see them.
I can't see shit.
This is actually...
I think we're dead.
I don't see how we can win.
This one...
I mean...
If we buy this, right?
We buy this.
We could reveal...
I feel like it's a little bit too late for that to pay off, actually.
It's not worth.
We gamble a little bit.
This is not, you know, buying anything in the shop.
This is just gambling.
It's different.
What was the other one?
No, I need range.
Have you seen the exit?
Go directly to jail.
Ooh, hey!
Angel, Angel!
No!
Oh, hold on.
Trade offer.
I take two black hearts, I lose two red hearts.
It's actually not a bad idea.
I'm taking it.
I will take that deal.
And maybe we get a little bit of...
Come on.
Question authority.
Oh, yeah, bombs.
Oh, you know what?
We have a bunch of bombs.
Let's go find a secret room.
Oh, no.
There's probably nothing here.
Okay, here we go.
I'm going to be in so much trouble here.
Just keep moving, keep moving.
Solid, solid.
Shit.
I...
I knew I shouldn't have picked this up.
I knew it.
It brings misfortune.
48 coins.
I have to buy things.
Why am I getting so little damage every time I find damage?
It's almost impossible to get my damage up.
I need to buy this.
I'm not...
We're saving money.
Oh, wait, this is the last...
It's the boss time now, isn't it?
Oh, nice.
Not bad at all.
Let's go see if we can find a secret room here.
Well, there it is.
And... ah...
Is there a second?
I know there's a second.
Where are you?
Actually, why am I not blowing these guys up?
Oh, uh... hmm, I could also re-roll.
Oh, yeah, that... right, that re-rolls it.
I was like, just give me some money at least.
I forgot about that.
Well, that's perfect.
This one is on sale.
More tears.
That's not gonna matter to me.
Less damage?
Absolutely not.
This is actually a sabotage.
Tarot card.
The lovers for me is useless.
Death.
That's 40 damage to everyone.
Maybe good.
I'm gonna buy one key.
Actually, two keys.
Remember, there's a bunch of doors in the last room.
I wanna have keys for that.
Let's go.
Ultra greed time.
So we have one extra life here.
That's something.
But it's... it's not good.
It's not good.
It's bad.
I mean, okay.
That was not bad at all.
I blow these guys up.
Money equals power.
This is gonna be a real tough one.
I think.
It's gotta be.
I mean, at least we can clear out coins pretty easily.
That's actually not too... Hold on, there's an item.
Hit up the...
Sorry, what?
Hold on.
Tears that enemies have a 5% chance.
Okay.
Hey!
Not bad!
Jesus Christ!
No!
Okay, that's pretty cool.
That's pretty cool.
This is actually dope as hell.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're not gonna... you're not gonna do that.
The more coins we collect, the more damage we deal.
It's all about money.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Yeah, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Very nice.
He's throwing coins at me.
I need to rearrange my shit.
There we go, that's a good one.
Good configuration.
Stop pirating!
Shit!
Death!
More coins, more damage.
Good.
We got adds.
Clear them out!
Holy shit!
I'm in trouble here, I'm in trouble here.
Dealing!
Come on, deal some damage.
According to script!
Beautiful!
Absolutely wonderful!
I almost opened the chest.
I almost opened the fucking chest, guys.
Okay, so, so...
Lucky pennies have appeared in the basement.
Uh, okay, let me just...
You unlock special hanging shopkeepers?
Alright.
Wooden nickel has appeared.
Okay.
I thought for sure some of these doors would open at least.
Maybe they do if you donate enough.
Wow.
Okay, well, I guess we just leave.
I have no bombs, I can't try to find secret rooms.
We're getting out of here.
Let's see if it's different now that we donated.
Nah, it's the same.
Skip.
Okay, well, so far so good.
I'm gonna take a small break here, guys.
I'll be back in like five minutes.
I'm back.
I think we may have had some technical issues in the first half here.
I disabled the ping guy so we don't get notified on Discord.
Sorry about that.
I just gobbled up a banana in record speed.
I'm actually gonna...
So we have a Jackiebot now on the server that's trying to catch scammers.
I'm gonna modify it to also make updates on livestreams and stuff.
And I'm gonna set it like a cooldown timer on it.
Such that when there's an update or when a livestream goes live that it can't ping again for at least like three or four hours.
You know, that way that's never gonna happen again.
I'm working on it.
Alright, uh, let's keep going.
Let's keep playing some Isaac.
Oh, yeah.
So that was a successful run.
Guys, I have the essays all in me.
We're doing a speedrun now.
On heart!
We're not gonna click greed again.
Here comes the speedrun.
We want to outrun the timer and see what happens.
This is something I've been wanting to do for a long time.
Speed!
Meow.
Kill them all.
Just go fast like a Ferrari.
Kill it, kill it, kill it.
Come on, this is way too slow.
Grab and go.
Nice.
Uh, this way.
There we go!
Oh, we grabbed this, of course.
See ya, nerd.
He's tired now.
I guess the rocks don't exist.
In our world.
HP up, we love it.
Go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Look, the timer's behind us already.
This guy's gonna poop something bad at me.
Eat the pill.
Insane.
Yep, we take this.
We don't care about that room.
Oh, wait, that was...
Nevermind, we do care about the room.
I thought it was a shop.
That's an item room.
We definitely care about that room.
That was an accidental rage bait right there.
That was not part of the scripted plan of rage baits today.
I don't even know what that is!
Number two?
Uh-oh.
What's that?
Firing continuously for three seconds, drops a butt bomb!
Oh, no!
Oh, I don't like that, actually.
That was bad.
I wasted a shot.
Actually, maybe it's okay with the bomb.
Go!
Oh, we can't.
We're not done.
You.
Oh, my God, it's Dingle.
Shit's about to hit the fan.
That's for you.
I'm trying to poop on him.
For some reason, he didn't want to lay a poop.
No, this was horrible.
This was horrible.
Dude, that's a crazy item, though.
Uh, what's that?
Whatever, I don't care.
We need HP.
Go!
That was a rainbow poop, as well.
Not sure what that was about.
We're ahead of the timer!
This is exciting.
The music here is so good.
One of my favorite tracks in the game.
Uh, which way?
Probably up here.
Oh, come on.
Huge.
That was a wasted floor thingy.
Oish!
Uh, hot bombs?
Sure.
Lay it safe.
But fast.
Uh, in here we're gonna take...
Uh, this one.
We're gonna grab... That's it.
Wait, this fire's in the way.
Oh, we're okay.
There's the boss.
I'm trying to put bombs on him.
Good.
No way!
Uh, act of contrition, uh, eternal heart allows angel rooms to appear even if they believe it's been taken on the dish and...
Wait, whoa, hold on.
Hold on a minute.
Allows angel rooms to appear even if a devil deal has been taken on the current run.
Deal chance reduction is decreased.
Now it's angel rooms.
Okay.
So, if you take a deal, it's like, confirmed.
There's no chance you're gonna get an angel.
Like, at all.
On the current run.
Ooh!
Hold on a minute, that's kinda big.
Let's just write that down so we don't forget this.
Uh, observations.
Taking deal, uh...
No angel for run.
That is kinda massive.
Uh, what's the other one?
Uh, that's the bible!
Uh...
I need to choose!
Bible!
We're bibling mom.
Bibling mom.
Speed, speed, speed, speed, speed, I didn't look at- Oh...
Actually, my damage is falling off a little bit here.
Uh, this way.
I don't like the fact that I'm pooping bombs when I'm holding the attack button.
It's making me worried for holding the attack button.
Which is something I like to do a lot on this character.
This way.
Was that an eternal heart?
Dude!
And do this!
What is going on here?
I'm actually gonna grab it and go to the boss.
We're not gonna come back for it.
We don't have time.
We're going.
Hard style!
Okay, okay, that was scary.
Fuck!
It happens.
Wow, look at all that HP!
Uh, this way.
Speed!
Where's the boss?
Gimme!
Sure.
Uh...
No, okay, I'm leaving.
Dude, this boss room is so hard to find.
What's that?
Uh...
Uh, no.
We roll.
Yeah.
Whatever.
That's good, that's good.
Here we go.
Wish me luck!
It smells like poop in here!
That's more HP.
We love it.
Look at the timer!
It's two rooms behind us!
Or floors.
We gotta be even faster!
I wanna be like five floors ahead of it.
Ah, okay, that's actually nice.
Uh, I think the boss is up here.
Look at him protecting the king up here in the corner.
Uh, here.
Shit.
Uh, uh, fuck, I'm going the wrong way.
Good thing we're moving fast.
That was bad.
That was bad?
What am I doing?
Focus, damn it!
There goes my black hearts.
Can I just throw a flashbang?
What do you want?
Dude, I'm going in every direction that isn't the boss.
Definitely consume that.
Range up, HP down, uh...
It's not that bad, actually.
Where is the boss?
Yeah, the bomb is flashbanging them.
Just lost a bunch of chances for devil stuff.
Okay.
I gotta sneeze.
Peering tears, we already had that, so it doesn't really matter.
Man, where are you?
A-Awas!
Uh, no, I don't want that.
The boss is behind the door.
I know it.
Man, these guys are just...
They have such a high rate of fire.
Mask of infamy, it's moi-
Joke, god.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna lay up the trap here.
That's for you.
Yeah, yeah, disorient them.
Beautiful.
Speed is actually okay.
Go.
Getting a little low on HP.
Ooh, the timer's catching up to us.
Just a bit.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Gimme that.
Thanks.
Arcade, why not?
Uh...
We don't have time for this.
Oh god, I'm conflicted.
Skatole?
Nice.
That's all I needed.
Fuck, what the hell is this?
We got Curse of the Bullshit right now.
Did not expect that.
Oh, no.
What the fuck?
I thought you were deactivated.
Ah, it's over.
We're done.
Up before- What did it say?
Whatever.
Gimme.
The Empress- What was that one?
Uh, damage.
We also have this one.
Uh...
Floor decoration.
This one.
Go.
Down with you.
Don't even think about it.
Mom's eyeshadow?
Just if I- Sure.
I'm in trouble.
It's not good.
Oish.
Oh, no.
The scissors!
Never run with those.
One more time.
I think I was a little bit too fast.
Little bit too fast.
This is the Azazel day.
We're doing full Azazel.
I definitely messed that up.
Big time.
Finally, I'm not pooping bombs anymore.
Oh, that feels amazing.
Oh, oh, okay.
Do you mind if I- Fucking open the chest!
Gimme- Oh, look at that!
Oh, no, no thanks.
Keep it!
Oh, I almost went in.
BLAH!
Bro, I can't- Okay, there we go.
I'm so used to my charge being less from the last run that I keep cancelling my attack before it's ready.
It's a problem.
Nice.
Dude, let's go for angels!
No deals!
Maximum angel.
Don't hit me.
Okay.
Oh, I cancelled it.
Jump at me, good, and then we kill.
Uh, oh, that's a fun one.
I like it.
Flush him out!
Oops.
Rainbow does whatever the rainbow does.
Nobody knows what it does.
It is a mystery for the ages.
It probably doesn't do anything.
It's just a fun little thing, you know?
Uh, oh, I have 16 coins?
Brother!
I have no- Oh, I don't have a goddamn thingy.
It's called a key.
Go!
Cute!
That's the boss.
Oh, look at this!
Sweetness.
I'm gonna flush him out!
Okay, it didn't do anything.
Worth a shot, though.
Wait, doesn't it usually have three of those little minions?
It's a dolly.
Uh, oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, go!
We're not taking deals, baby.
I'm not even gonna look!
Fast, fast, fast.
Bad spot.
Whoops!
What was this one?
The fool, I actually like that more.
Yeah, I like it more.
Oi, oi, oi.
There we go, let's see what we get.
Question mark.
I don't believe that.
Cross blast plus five bombs?
Oh, that one!
Wait, so it's laser now, or- No, okay, it's just a cross blast.
Normal bomb, I see.
No, thanks.
I reject the bomb.
That's right.
Uh, nineteen coins.
We take this one.
Pokey go, gotta catch him all.
Can't let the start of each new room to summon a permanent recharm monster.
Nice, nice, nice.
Let's move.
Want a strict timer here?
No time for dilly-dallying.
Uh, watch battery?
Increase chance of a little battery spawning.
Chance of a place of room reward with a...
I mean, okay.
I guess I didn't have a trinket, so it's fine.
That's amazing.
R key, time to- What?
Oh, wait!
You can restart with R, right?
R key is consumed to restart the run, sending Isaac back to the first floor, but with all of the collected items retained.
Uh, what?
R key is consumed to restart the run.
Sending Isaac back to the first floor, but with- Ooh!
I wonder if I get sent back in time as well, so I'm still ahead of the timer.
You know?
Oh, wait a minute, what's happening?
We got problems!
Are we crashing again?
Hello, hello, check, check.
Mic check.
Are we good?
Did it crash again?
Guys, you missed it all, man.
You missed it.
I picked up an item called an R key, and I held down R, and I restarted the whole game.
Nah, I'm kidding, come on.
Come on, nah, I didn't do that.
Who do you think I am, huh?
I mean, it's kind of cool, in essence, what I just read there, but I like to flush.
We're going for the boss now.
We're going to try and flush this boss.
It didn't get flushed.
That's a lot of bombs.
That's a lot of bombs!
Nice.
Midnight snack, HP up, lovely.
We're not taking any deals.
I'm not taking the devil deal!
Nope!
I don't care what was in there, I'm not taking it.
Ain't nobody got time for this.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Really?
How are you not dead?
That is actually unreal.
Uh, just to find...
Yeah, I think it's better.
Maybe.
We gotta go fast.
Get poison, nerd!
We can take a peek in here.
I've had a peek.
Yeah!
Gimme.
Boss is down here.
No, it's not.
Shit.
I went the wrong way.
Maybe I like the fool more.
Gimme!
I actually really needed that.
Nice.
Treasure room.
Uh, yeah!
Damage.
Oh, that's massive.
That is so big.
We're really doing well here.
This is a dream.
Go!
It is the Carrion Quain.
I'm gonna...
Flush him!
Wait, who can I flush?
Oh, wait.
I can probably flush Dingle.
He's a boob!
I'm gonna flush him out of the toilet.
Obviously!
We're gonna flush the boob.
The turd.
Oh, no.
Angel!
Oh my god, I keep hitting these.
What's that?
The Goblet of...
One health.
Oh, wait, I can fly already.
That's fine.
Oh, gimme that.
Let's go!
We are two floors ahead of the timer.
What are we gonna get at the end?
Maybe it's like a guaranteed unlock.
You know?
That's what I think.
We have darkness, though.
That's gonna mess with us.
That's not good.
Not good at all.
Not going there.
Do not go in there.
Nope.
Very unlucky with the first two rooms.
Yes.
Flush him!
Oh, not everyone got flushed.
Nice.
Wow!
What's your luck at that one?
Wait, why am I destroying fires?
There's no need to do that.
Okay.
What do we got?
Some kind of one-tooth item.
Bumbo familiar, the one's around consuming coins.
Uh, can never stop as it consumes coins.
Uh, yeah, why not?
That sounds fun.
Consume all the coins you want, friend.
Nope!
Mistake.
Boss, go!
We're gonna try and flush him anyway.
Let's see what happens.
Actually, I should have waited for ads.
And probably flushed the ads.
Look at the little guy inside!
You saw that?
Hey, come here.
Dude, you are so annoying.
Uh, the photo...
Yeah, okay.
Uh, go.
We're gonna get an extra heart, because we have an eternal.
Three floors ahead of the timer.
Meow.
Grab it all.
I see...
Okay, I don't see any special rocks.
We move.
What?
What's that?
Aquarius, leave the trailer creep.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, that's cool.
Copies the effects.
I thought for a second we're gonna get laser creep.
Aye, aye, aye.
Flush him.
Oh.
Did work against this guy.
He's too big.
He doesn't fit in the toilet.
Lighter.
And click burn on enemy.
What is the current one?
Poison tears?
I actually kinda like poison tears.
Call me crazy.
I think they're cool.
That guy dies.
This guy...
Everyone dies.
Ha!
Camouflage!
No!
Yes!
Lord of the Pit!
Oh, we can already fly.
Okay, I'm not falling for this one again.
Uh...
Response locus... shift... shift...
I'll be taking that.
This one is...
Uh, we don't need that.
I'm good, thanks.
See ya.
Oh my goodness.
Oh!
Dang it all.
Here we go!
Mon-time!
And we are in good time.
I keep thinking this guy is one of my enemies, but he's not.
Dude, the creep is doing so much damage.
Oh, look!
We've already been in there.
Oh, is that what...
okay!
I had this before once!
I do... uh, let's not, you know, assume immediately that this is what's happening.
But I'm gonna kinda assume.
Could be a coincidence.
The place is tears with a charge shot that increases in size and damage the longer it is held.
Wait.
The longer it is held?!
Dude, I am the master of holding!
Oh,
that's a... that's a massive beam we have there.
It may not be better.
Oh, we're doing this wave thing.
Fifteen waves.
With no HP.
This is gonna be tough, guys.
I'm gonna die here.
There is no way.
He splits?
Use the terrain to my advantage?
We're using hit-and-run tactics.
Now, what?!
Oh, this guy, I didn't even see him!
That's crazy.
Those are enemies.
I like the music.
Dude, the creep I leave on the floor is kinda...
nice.
Doing a lot of damage here.
The hit-and-run tactics are especially good with this beam here, because the beam is so short-lived.
You pretty much get the entire effect out of it when you run at full speed, you know?
It's so wide, too.
Oh, he got...
That's going pretty well!
Oh, no!
What the hell is that?!
A bony fish!
I can fly.
I mean, HPs are dropping.
It's really nice.
We got the Devil and the Angel.
How come they're not fighting each other?
They're teaming up to take me out, as if I'm somehow worse.
Even they will find, you know, camaraderie in the face of this evil here that I am.
Oh, man.
Kill him!
Oh, that was the wrong direction.
Nice!
I mean, if they keep giving me healing, then...
This is going to be much easier than I thought.
I'm not going to say it's easy, though.
Because it definitely isn't.
One of them is down.
Two of them is down.
This guy is dangerous, though.
The way he jumps is really bad for me.
I'm so focused!
Wait, I wonder if I can shoot...
Oh, I can still shoot without a full charge!
Good to know.
I don't need to go all the way.
Nice, nice.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was bad.
I messed it up.
I fudged it up, guys.
Just calm down.
There's no reason to panic here.
We're doing great.
Just take it easy.
Think about the situation.
Look for some help, you know?
Do we have any more blue HP lying around somewhere?
Doesn't look like it.
14 out of 15!
This guy needs to die.
Oi, oi, oi.
Oh, he died in the creep or what?
The nail has appeared in the basement.
And we get Charm of the Vampire.
He holds half a Red Heart for every 13 enemies killed.
That's not that great.
But we did it.
We have done it.
Let's see if that's just a coincidence, though.
More is going to happen here.
Wait, I can go back in.
I can go again?
Imagine if I can go again.
Just keep choosing items.
Guess we move on.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can do the Fool, actually.
What happens if I go back?
Nah.
Maybe I'll blow this thing up.
Also, let's just keep going.
I need to see if the timer's still active.
Not this way, this way.
Take me to... down here.
I have to remember that I have... Why didn't I use Flush?
In that fight!
Holy shit, bro.
Not sure if I even could have used Flush, but you know.
Maybe I could have.
Some of the enemies were small.
Also, there was no timer on the thing, so I think the timer is related to what we just did.
If you beat the timer, you get to have that little boss fight there.
And get an extra item if you're good enough.
Touch a little annoying guy.
Okay, this way.
Oh, no, we're lost!
Die!
Whoa.
Oh, that's a friend.
Okay.
Ho ho!
Oh, lordy.
What about this way?
Dude, my laser is so powerful.
It's like a nuke is hitting every time.
A frowning?
Something had appeared?
Huh?
I didn't get to read it.
I don't know what that means.
Alright, just keep going.
A vis appears!
What is a vis?
Oh, my god.
A visage?
Maybe.
Uh, where am I going?
This way?
Hey!
Death and...
Ooh, that's nice.
Soulheart.
The Hierophant.
Flush him!
I don't like your kind.
You go down the toilet.
Sick.
Oh, the boss is here.
Teratoma!
What?
He got nuked!
Oh, wow.
I got some good damage here.
Placenta is actually pretty cool.
I like it.
Now, wait, wait, wait.
Do we take a deal?
I mean, I can take a look, I guess.
Wait, what?
Hello?
Why are there no deals?
Where are my deals at?
Oh, hey!
Look at that!
Okay, that was totally worth it.
What the... Alright.
Sick.
Now it's time for the final boss.
Well, final boss.
But, you know.
You know what I mean.
Yudero.
Flush him.
He's fucking... Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Careful.
Careful now.
That was scary.
Uh, let's go... here.
Okay, I got 35 coins.
I'll definitely do some gambling.
Gamble my life savings away.
Gamble it all.
Give me an item.
Oh, Blackheart!
You're the best!
Oh my god, I'm rich.
This is amazing.
Yeah, dude!
Oh, whoops.
This is the risk of standing too close to it.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Blow that up.
Sometimes there's like blue hearts in those when you blow them up.
Not this time, though.
Flush!
Such a nice combo.
Flush him and gush him, you know, with the laser.
Give me
that key.
I got so many friends with me.
Mystery egg has appeared!
What the... I feel like I'm getting so many upgrades.
Suddenly I'm just getting showered with that stuff.
Kill him.
Something has appeared?
I didn't get to read it.
Oh man, this is something else.
Oh, Eternal Heart!
Oh, you know I take that.
Oh, appear, please.
Don't be like that.
Oh my god, I got hit.
Pathetic.
Flush him.
They cannot be flushed.
Good to know.
Oh, nice!
Uh, let's go.
It lives.
I'm gonna fuck him up.
Oh wait, I don't need to wait for the full charge.
I'm an idiot.
There we go.
And there's one more.
I kill it.
Nice.
There's one more.
And now we go ham.
Look at that damage.
Not bad at all.
The depths are dank?
Did it say dank?
The depths are dank.
Oh, we're going down, baby.
We're not going up.
We're going down.
But wait, what's this?
Oh, I can remove all my guys.
Imagine.
Holy shit.
Brimston is mine.
Dark bomb and the Flusher.
We like the Flusher.
Um, okay, go.
Wait, there was a... There was something on the left!
There was a fucking hole in the wall!
Oh my god.
The fucking place got turned into a hole.
I came out and then it was different.
Oh well.
It's fine.
I'm gonna live without that item.
It's probably just gonna be another 15 waves, right?
But that begs the question.
If you beat the timer and you beat those 15 waves, you can, like, keep beating a timer.
Except the timer wasn't there, so I don't know about that.
But you keep beating the timer and then you can keep trying to do those 15 waves every floor onwards and get the chance or opportunity to get a nice item.
If you're good enough and you want to risk it, right?
It's risk reward.
Oh, this guy's gonna consume all my red hearts.
I don't know if I like that, actually.
Oh, we're gonna destroy these.
Not lucky.
Never lucky.
Look
at the range I have now.
Oh yeah, I have Brimstone!
Fuck, I was like, wait a minute, my range is kind of wild.
What happened there?
But I guess the Brimstone happened, right?
Kill him!
Okay.
We're gonna keep going faster, by the way.
I want to see what else can happen.
We're speeding, speeding and speeding.
Sick.
I love the way the screen shakes when I use my attack now.
It is that powerful, you know?
Here we go.
Satan.
Let's not fuck this up.
We got good items here.
I'm gonna flush him.
Okay.
Didn't do anything.
Oh, I got Brimstone too, motherfucker!
Maybe that's where I got it from.
He has the Brimstone, you know?
That's the original Brimstone guy.
We're not done, we're not done.
He's gonna go... Oh, I can also start bombing, actually.
I'm just gonna keep bombing like this.
Dude, the bombs are the strategy?!
That's how you do it, of course!
Because he's gonna keep hitting where you were, right?
Like two seconds ago.
It's actually perfect.
Holy shit.
What a run.
Many personalities.
Yeah, you're fighting yourself down there.
In that basement.
Literally, we are fighting ourselves at some point.
Nice.
Nice, nice!
Let's do a random.
I'm feeling it, baby.
I feel it in my bow.
Let's do this one, then.
Maybe we'll do some stepping, depending on what we find.
Kind of want to do the step and find the keys!
That's another big mystery.
You know what?
I wonder if there's a difference.
Let's say I were to go fast again, but with a different character.
Maybe something different happens.
Because I'm pretty sure the last time that happened, I was on a Seizel, too.
No, actually, I wasn't.
I was on that tank character, right?
Or someone who was healing a lot.
With the bombs, if you remember.
Yeah, never mind.
Botfly, that's a really good one.
Definitely taking that.
We are poor.
Let me actually try and speed up a little bit.
I'm not going to go like, super speed mode.
I'm just going to speed up a little bit.
Just a tiny fraction, I'm out.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wonderful.
It's kind of hard to speed up when you're not a Seizel, you know?
You can't really kill things fast.
Yeah, walk into the fire, nerd.
Dumbass.
Okay.
Let's go.
We're doing semi-speed run.
This guy's going to take 10 million years to kill, though.
Maybe it can be more aggressive, because my little botfly is going to protect me, right?
At least I think so.
It's not doing anything right now.
Botfly!
Help me!
I'm going to bomb him.
Sick!
That's how you get speed.
Nice.
Guys, we're doing angels.
I love the angels.
I'm an angel man now.
No more demons.
I have written demons off completely from my life.
I'm a multi-angel man.
I'm a man.
I think.
It's okay.
You know I'd be eating pills.
Dude, is my damage suddenly dogshit?
No, it's still 2.62.
This guy
is a proper tank.
Come here.
You gonna jump at me?
Yeah.
Oh, this room is insane.
I am going to lose a lot of HP here, unless I play this beautifully.
Oh my god.
How the fuck is anyone supposed to do this room?
Oh, I think we're good.
We made it.
Barely.
No healing though.
Oh man.
I'm gonna be safe here.
I'm safe here.
Oh, that was close.
Do not poop on me.
We gotta get some HP here.
Thank you, bird.
That's huge.
That's all I needed.
Wait, no treasure?
We gotta get the treasure though.
Treasure is a must right now.
We gotta do it.
As long as I stay at range here, they're not gonna bother me too much.
Oh, careful not to blow yourself up.
I eat it.
I'm being not rewarded here.
Four coins.
Now I'm not gonna go to the shop.
Let's see if it's actually possible to outrun the timer on this character.
If we don't find...
I mean, it's gonna be dependent on what items we get, right?
If we get some good damage.
Not bad.
That was smooth.
Do you think?
Dude, okay.
I'm gonna set a trap for him.
Thought of being so clever.
No!
I'm terrible at timing it.
You're gonna do an attack?
No way.
Oi!
Yeah, that was not great.
But that's great.
That is really great.
We don't take deals.
We don't make deals with terrorists.
Now, angels.
That's another story.
I take that deal any day.
Nope.
That's a lot of self-harm and run room there.
Dude, my shot speed is down to shit right now.
Look out!
It's like slow motion.
Oh, this room is gonna take eight million years.
Dude, this glass of milk is kind of saving me right now.
Or maybe it's the fly.
Maybe both, actually.
There we go.
Nothing in here.
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
I don't think we are able to outrun the timer.
The contrast is...
really crazy when you just come from Azazel, you know?
Okay.
Okay, just do it.
Here we go.
Pesty
lawns.
Actually, I don't think I need to worry about the projectiles because I have my buddies protecting me.
Ah, never mind.
It's not perfect.
Don't throw it now.
Good stuff.
Fall of bandages.
And we move on.
Yay, I love this map.
We're actually ahead of the timer.
I am so surprised at that.
I thought for sure we would be so far behind.
Guys, I may be addicted to speedrunning now.
I'm not gonna lie, like, getting that item and the waves is...
It's a lot of fun.
I may have to do it every time now.
Destroy that tomato!
No tomato can be this big.
Nothing dropped because I heard it.
This shot speed though is killing me.
Slowly from inside.
Oh yeah, that was bad.
I shouldn't have gone down there.
Dead end.
Oh, what the...
No lock so far.
Treasure room me.
He's gonna try and poop on me.
Oh, these guys can relocate.
But they can only be in the water.
Not too bad.
Five coins.
I don't know.
Maybe... yeah, I actually like these.
Okay, well...
Actually, I'm not too sad about that.
Shot speed, though, is the next one I want to get up.
I can almost outrun my own shots.
Okay, I was afraid of a laser.
Beautiful.
It's Pape!
What's up, Pape?
Oh shit, I stepped on the poop!
I made a mistake.
At least I'm doing extra damage now.
Don't hit me, don't hit me!
Thank you!
I think the milk just...
No, the bot just protected me there.
Thanks, thanks.
Oh, we haven't found a treasure room.
I gotta get it.
Shouldn't take long.
Down here.
No, it's not even here.
Shit!
Soul hearts!
Actually, so good.
I love when the guitar comes in.
The layered music.
Dude,
I'm getting so unlucky with the freaking treasure room here.
Sick.
There it is.
Oh my god!
Dingle is single.
I shouldn't throw stones when I live in a glass house.
Ah, sure.
Show me what's good.
X-ray vision!
I do like that.
Let's see if it reveals something on the way.
You heard that?
I heard it.
It's okay.
We're leaving.
No, we're not.
Not yet.
We're definitely behind now, though.
Oh, we could step.
There's no stepper, of course.
Of course there's not.
Not that I've seen, though.
We move.
No, the timer's ahead of us!
We gotta hurry now.
We gotta go faster.
We may have to be lying direct for the boss.
Oh no, this room is gonna...
Jesus!
Dude, this botfly is working overtime.
Kill these guys first, actually.
I don't want to deal with the little guys while these guys are shooting stuff at me.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Pandora's box has been opened!
Good, good, good, good.
Nice.
Damn tomatoes.
They're not even ripe!
Shit!
It was almost perfect, what I did.
Kinda rich, though.
See, it hurts.
No, it got closed off!
The freaking wall had a...
You know, what do you call it, a cave-in?
I haven't seen that before.
To be fair, though, I think if you want to speedrun with this character, you kinda want to activate a horn-ness.
So you deal more damage, right?
And you want to stay on low HP, get some soul hearts, get some banjos going, you know?
Okay, finally.
Let's see what we got.
No!
We don't have time for this!
Okay, you like bombs?
This is for you.
Shit!
Okay, this is for you!
Thank you.
Uh, no thanks.
This way...
Go north.
Oh, what the hell is this?
I don't like this room at all.
I like this room.
No, is this Sprinkle a dude?
I mean, I guess we don't have anything else.
You know who uses the Sprinkle?
Dingle.
Of course he does.
Come on, sprinkle them.
Kill them for me, please.
Yo, this room is actually kinda...
messing with me.
There is no way we're gonna catch up to the timer.
What?
Maybe up here?
Okay, I like that.
Shit.
Limited space to operate.
They're gonna charge me.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, that'll speed things up.
Not to find the boss.
Oh, no.
Nice.
Show me what's good.
Oh, we've been there already.
Man, I need healing.
This can't go on like this!
Sprinkle them.
Where are these bombs coming from?
What is happening?!
Oh, my sprinkler!
The worst item in the game!
Never pick up the sprinkler.
I'm telling you, don't never pick up the fucking sprinkler.
It will bite you in the ass.
Oh.
I can't believe that.
Oh, it's Isaac.
Okay.
We're speed running.
Oh, not like this.
Can we kill this guy?
Bro, I'm gonna die in this room.
I'm not gonna die in this room.
I will survive.
What is that song?
There you go.
I will survive.
It's a good song.
I like this song.
He's in a very annoying spot right here.
This is vexing me to a very large degree.
Bro!
Dude, this room sucks ass.
This is the worst.
Are you kidding me right now?
Like...
Okay, I've had enough of your shit.
We blow him up.
Ain't nobody got time for that.
What is that?
120 volt.
1.21 gigawatts!
Electrifies Isaac, automatically sapping enemies in close range for a lot of damage.
The saps can chain up to four additional nearby enemies.
Cool.
That is an American outlet, by the way.
For those that don't know.
In fact, I think everyone knows.
Because if you're American, you know it.
And if you're not American, you also know.
Because it's not your plug.
Okay.
We're fine.
Doesn't it look like we have a party hat on?
Nice.
Not bad.
No, no, we're speedrunning.
No time for that.
Uh, maybe we kill these first, actually.
Ooh!
Okay!
Oh, that's sick!
Yo!
Really good against these small guys.
Chain lightning.
I'm a shaman.
Ah!
Uh!
I can't get in there.
We're going!
It's pinned.
One, two, three, four.
That was bad.
I really tried to get them there, but I messed it up.
Yo, the electricity is kind of doing work.
Yeah!
Not bad.
Okay, check this out.
Eh, good enough.
Okay.
We are officially on par with the timer.
Yeah, laser them.
You got to be really close for that to work, though.
I was actually kind of sick when you get really close.
But the nation, I don't think so, buddy.
I'm not donating shit.
I'm actually going to get in real close here, then.
Oh, maybe not that close.
I just lost a whole heart.
Whoop, whoop, whoop.
That was a thingy.
Tidded rock, but we don't have bombs, so whatever.
Oh, losing my mind here.
Blow him up.
Right there, there's a secret.
Oh, he's on a bomb.
I thought that was a bomb spider.
Sir, do you mind coming here?
Okay, this thing needs to die now.
Ah, what a room.
Butt bombs.
I don't like that.
We're going to re-roll that.
Yep.
Man, the electricity is kind of banging.
That's a banger.
And mash.
I actually never had that.
It sounds so good when you say it, though.
I've also never been to Nando's, or been cheeky.
I'd love to try it.
Many things in life that I want to try.
Okay, I'm actually going to risk it.
Electrify!
Okay, maybe that's a bit too risky.
That was a bit too risky.
Go back and re-roll.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Not a bad re-roll at all!
Wait a minute.
Let me confirm.
I should be healing myself, actually.
I'm going to grab a bomb from here.
Yeah!
Wait, though.
Hold on.
Yes.
Go for it.
It's the hunt!
Oh, I didn't mean to push that away from me.
Nice.
Oh, kind of.
Okay, okay.
We're good, we're good.
Oh, that's fantastic.
Love getting that.
Alrighty then.
Moving on.
Imagine we get the bombs now.
I want that.
The fetus.
Starring Norman Reedus.
Actually, that battery is kind of clutch here.
Find a treasure room soon?
Okay, then.
I will say I'm lacking damage.
Like, if not for the electricity, it's kind of rough out here, you know?
I'm going to be honest with you.
This I can do.
Goat hoof!
Speed up.
Alright.
Ah, one more.
Yeah!
Something's wrong.
Oh, everything's fine.
What do you mean?
This room is not good for my blood pleasure.
Did I say blood pleasure?
I swear I'm not blood drunk.
I swear it's...
Come on.
Oh yeah, I should have electrified them.
They're just approaching slowly.
Minisingly.
I feel like I'm exploring all the worst areas first.
Oh yeah, do that.
Electrify him.
Here we go.
Ah, that's bullshit.
Re-roll!
Oh, I like that one.
Let's see them secrets.
There it is.
Oh, nice.
Okay, I'm gonna grab that.
Oh, it's Pilfiesta.
Friends till the end.
Alright.
So if I do this in here...
Wait, I don't have money anyway!
What am I doing?
I messed up.
I messed up big time.
That was a waste.
I was like, I'm gonna buy this now.
Look at all my money.
I don't trust electricity here.
They're gonna poop on me with the green stuff and I'm gonna have a bad time.
Actually, wait a minute.
I think I'm immune to creep on this floor.
The water nullifies it.
Get electrified.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm down, calm down.
You know what I want to do?
I want to get an angel room and then I want to re-roll.
That's the frickin' plan.
Makes me want to chub.
Oh god.
I feel like without the electricity against this guy, I'm not gonna do anything, you know?
But I guess it is chain lightning.
I could also just re-roll the item he's gonna spawn here, which wouldn't be a bad idea.
Man, this guy's tanky.
Oi, oi, oi.
Oh my god.
How did I not get hit?
I feel like his hitbox is smaller than it seems.
Like much smaller.
Good stuff, good stuff.
Yeah, that's good.
Get some of those base stats up.
Not gonna re-roll that one.
I mean, we're kind of catching up to the time a little bit, but not quite.
We gotta be even faster.
Yo.
Chain reaction.
Now, we don't have time for that.
Oh, did you see that?
That's a lot of damage there.
Amazing.
I don't like any of this.
I could blow this up.
This battery could come in handy, perhaps.
Let's keep in mind there's a battery there.
Points.
There's the boss.
We can re-roll quite a bit in here.
Wait, the electricity is like super nice against this guy because he's so big.
I don't have to be that close to him, you know?
It is like 80% of my damage right now.
Very nice.
I mean, this is a mate.
I gotta take it, man.
Fuck.
They keep giving me two good items.
They're too good.
Let's find a treasure room and re-roll that instead.
That's the plan now.
Also, secrets, right?
We can find those with these glasses.
I want to find them all.
All right.
Ah, grab it.
Electrify them.
I'm actually a big fan of this electrification.
Haven't found a single secret.
Speak enough.
These are gonna blow up in my face, yeah.
Dude, I actually forgot that I could heal with bombs.
Like, I totally forgot I had that because I haven't had bombs for a while, you know?
I totally forgot.
I'm glad the game just reminded me.
Where is this treasure room?
Oh my god, please.
I was playing very bad there.
Yeah, that was sick.
Open up, buddy.
That's a lot of healing for me.
Wait, if I do this...
I didn't mean to do that.
I meant, if I give him this, a bunch of bomb spawn and then walk into everything to get full health.
I wonder if there's like a cooldown on it.
That's why I tried it, you know?
So if I get healed, maybe there's like a tiny cooldown where I can't get healed again, you know?
But you can stack it, it seems.
Here we go.
Reroll time?
Yeah, I don't like that.
That's the Dead Sea Scroll?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
What the fuck?
Where's my battery at?
Did I accidentally use this item?
Did I press space accidentally?
I don't understand.
I must have.
I must have clicked the button accidentally at some point.
Why not?
Fuck it.
I feel like we can't catch up to the timer anyway.
At this point, you know, it's...
We're a little too slow.
And we had another one all the way at the end.
Okay.
Well, we found both secret rooms anyway.
Fuck it.
Let's grab the battery.
Reroll and move on.
That was insane parkour just now.
Precision inputs.
Wait, where am I?
Right down here.
Saga pennies?
That is absolutely horrible.
Not a big fan.
I would say I'm a medium fan.
A 18 centimeter in the radius fan.
This way.
It's kind of a big fan, actually.
You need to die.
Awesome.
That's more healing.
I thought we were closer to the end here.
Okay, we caught up to the timer.
I mean, we still have a chance, I think.
We got to speed it up here.
Speed.
Speed, speed, speed.
Let's, you know, pedal to the pedal or whatever.
You know the expression.
I'm getting rich somehow.
You know what?
Let me blow this up.
I know I'm on a tight schedule here, bud.
Hold on now.
Destroying blue fire opens fight club.
Fuck yeah, man.
That's awesome.
Doing nothing for my electricity.
Nice.
What do you got?
I should not get close to these guys, actually.
Or should I?
Live dangerously.
Get rewarded.
This is going to be so fun with the electricity.
Hahaha.
I love this.
Man, I'm taking too much damage, though.
That was kind of bad.
I should have done that.
A little too risky.
Okay.
I wonder if this electricity scales with my damage.
Let me see.
Yeah, 75% tear damage.
That is crazy.
We need to up our tear damage here.
Even more.
Let me in.
What the heck is that?
Uh, here.
Evil charm.
Lock up.
Plus, I feel protected.
Grants limited immunity to enemy creep and fireplaces, allowing Isaac to touch them for up to one second before taking damage.
Oh, that's very good for me.
I need that so badly.
We're going to blow these fuckers up.
Okay, we're fine.
What's this?
Sup, dudes?
Okay, that was a bit risky.
Kill him!
Losing too much HP here for no reason.
Tentify tears that temporarily shrink enemies.
Shrink enemies that can be...
No!
Sure.
Whatever.
I'm not too excited about that one, though.
We don't have time for this.
Take these and go right.
Electricity?
Nice.
No, thanks.
Hey, come here.
Hee hee hee!
I am immune.
You can't hurt me.
God, it's like a waltz when I electrify these fools.
I'm going left.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
34 coins.
Please be good.
I need batteries.
Uh, let me see here.
Actually, wait up, wait, wait.
This will heal me.
For the D6, though.
It didn't heal me.
I guess the shockwave is not the same as an explosion.
Oh, right, it's for the whole floor.
Oh, that scared me.
Uh, destroyed poops.
No, I hit that.
Give me this back.
Where do we go?
Let's go this way.
The shockwave will hurt enemies or...
Dude, love it.
We're going to shock them.
We're going to electrify them.
I love that effect.
Okay, it's time to reroll the boss stuff.
This has got to be Angel.
Half HP gone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
That's cool.
You're dead, though.
No, my range is good.
Reroll.
Dude, am I lucky or what?
Four?
Luck?
Holy.
Wait a minute.
I know I said we were on a timer, but I just want to shockwave this last room here.
Real bad.
And get this HP.
This is plus full health.
Oh, wait, that was a secret.
We can step.
Nope.
I mean, we can go to the room in the bottom right, but I don't really want to do that.
That was a mistake just now.
We don't have time to heal.
We got bombs for that.
The timer's gone.
I think we fucked it up.
Yeah, we're too late.
Whoa.
It's an area.
Wait, why am I tears like this?
The area is messing with my tears.
Wait, what's happening here?
Huh?
I don't know what just happened.
Five luck!
Have you ever seen anyone as lucky as this?
I don't think so.
I should play the lottery.
What is this place?
They're being squished!
Oh, that's too bad, guys.
Squished and electrified.
Oh, shit, I'm being squished now, too.
Oh, no.
Yeah, this room is actually horrible.
I don't like it.
I should have made fun of them.
The same thing happened to me afterwards, you know?
This is what happens.
Don't make fun of little...
creatures like that.
This guy's gonna throw bones at me.
And not the good kind.
Bastards.
Let's combine the healing with finding secrets.
But I guess my glasses are gonna do that anyway.
Come here.
Why got pushed out of the room?
How does that even happen?
The door was closed.
Wait, how did that just happen?
Oh, I don't like the darkness here.
Make me nervous.
I can't believe there's still new areas.
Like, this game is crazy.
Okay, we got a battery up there, so we can totally do a re-rolling spree.
Electrify!
Before they charge!
Ah, damn.
These rooms are kind of nuts.
This layout is something else.
Oh, wait, the bombs are good for me.
Fuck me.
I keep forgetting.
It's such a hard habit to get rid of.
Wait, I should just run into them, actually.
I actually know, because I take a little bit of damage before they explode, so it evens out.
Not a good idea.
But you do want to get close to them and then shoot them.
What is that?
Quints.
First five enemies killed in each room will spawn a random friendly baby.
I am not a big fan of that.
Taurus.
While in a room with enemies, Isaac gains a star.
I mean, this one is kind of good, but I kind of want to re-roll.
Yeah.
Also, we have an eternal heart.
No, that's a blue heart.
I thought that was a full battery.
Maybe I'll take it then.
Nah, we're gonna see if we can get more battery.
Heal me.
Very nice.
Oh, right.
Secret.
Ah, I turned around and did that thing.
Can't believe it.
Also, where's all my shops at?
Gotta spend this money.
As long as I keep finding bombs, I'm happy.
We can go re-roll in just a second here.
This way.
Then again, I mean, running into enemies is actually kind of a synergy with the electrify that I have.
And maybe I save the re-roll for the boss.
Depends on how many rooms we have left here.
Wait, is that the third secret we found?
That can't be, right?
Let me see.
No, it's not, okay.
Not bad.
Wait, what is this room?
Huh.
Here we go.
Starter deck?
No.
What is that one?
Wooden nickel.
50% chance to...
Oh.
All right.
Oh, well.
I am going to buy this and re-roll.
But...
Yes.
Very good.
And then we have this guy.
Nice.
Dude, I'm rich.
The sun!
Not bad at all.
This was a great job.
Holy shit.
Not bad at all.
You know what?
I'm going to go grab that Taurus thing.
I have decided.
It's a good synergy with the electricity.
There you are.
The devil.
Nah.
Show me your face.
Really?
Boss is here.
Let me get the Taurus first.
And some more battery, of course.
Actually, yeah, definitely.
There's a couple rooms left.
Music is very...
I don't even know.
What's that?
Half battery.
Oh, man.
We actually cannot get full battery.
That's crazy.
Unless there's something up here.
Let's check that out.
Yeah, not that great.
Let's go grab this item.
Perhaps killing the boss will grant two charges.
And we can re-roll after.
Man, it's so hard to navigate in the dark.
Wait, did I say speed down?
Yeah.
I guess that's the trade-off.
I actually want to get this card and use it on the boss here and then switch it out.
Here we go.
There's something in my mouth!
Fuck!
I have to put my hand off the...
Yeah, why didn't I just pause?
Here we go!
Yeah, you like that, son?
Okay, we're done with that now.
The
synergies...
It's actually not going super well here.
I'm taking too much damage!
I can't see anything in the dark.
Peel up.
Just in case I forget later.
We gotta stay on the move here.
Mom's foot is gonna come down any second.
Good stuff!
Go!
Okay, then.
Woom!
Like,
my damage is good here.
But...
My tears are terrible.
And shot speed.
I wonder!
Fuck!
You know what, I need the speed.
I feel like I'm super slow without it.
Good.
Dude, you can kind of use bombs to block people off.
Oh god.
Bro!
If you just stand still, he's not even gonna hit you.
That's the funny part.
I
gotta heal a little bit.
Just a tad.
Brother man!
No way.
What?!
This room can suck my ass.
This is actually insane.
Let me outta here!
Holy shit.
Okay, man.
Fuck.
What a way to end.
That was terrible.
I was trying to save my son as well.
Like an idiot.
I should've just used it.
Ah, man.
Forgot about pyro.
No, I was healing myself at the end there with the pyro.
I was just too, uh...
What do you call it?
Foolish.
Going in with 1 HP.
Oh yeah, rage bait!
What did you think?
That I do a good job of rage baiting today, intentionally.
You liked it?
You unintentionally caused some people to rage quit the stream.
No, no, no.
Intentionally.
I did that intentionally.
It wasn't unintentional.
It was the plan.
10 out of 10.
Nice.
Good stuff.
Would you say this rage bait was worse or better than normal?
S-tier, peak rage bait.
Scripted greed donation run.
Wait, which one was that?
The one where I didn't get to deposit anything or the one where I did deposit something?
I think both were kind of good.
Give you a script writer a race.
Nice!
I'm getting more money!
Oh wait, no, the intern.
Accidentally doing greed and assasal.
Oh yeah, oh that's true!
Yeah, I wanted to do speedrun and then I went it.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Greed with half a health left was insane.
Right?
That was so close.
And I got so much money out of it too.
I deposited so much money into that box.
Have you tried connection bonding to tackle your streaming outages?
Well, connection bond...
You mean like having two internet connections?
I'm actually gonna switch my internet provider.
Because I can't stand this anymore.
It's not on me, it's not my computer.
Like it's 100% the internet.
Either that or twitch.
Because my internet is totally fine like 24-7.
But it's hard to say, I don't...
I don't know.
I don't know why it's happening.
Having one wired and one satellite.
You know what, I'm gonna look into that actually.
Because the stream going out is pissing me off.
At least the VOD is not affected at this point, but...
Yeah.
Oh, I forgot about the gym mod, sorry.
You're right, I should have activated that.
In fact, I'm gonna do it now.
So...
Gym button.
Yeah, it's fine.
Just let me do it.
There it is.
It has been enabled.
It's because the game tried to update me to the version that is apparently bugged.
So I had to revert, and when you do that, I guess this resets that setting.
Gym mod gives plus nine luck.
We'll see about that next time, when I find nothing.
Can you confirm that buying more options in the challenge where treasure room can't spawn was biggest scripted rage?
No.
I mean, yes.
That was actually...
I came up with that script, and even my internet was like, dude, that's brilliant.
You should definitely go with that.
And you know, we made it the highlights.
That was like, it was a work in progress over like a couple days.
But yeah, we got the script together, and that was it, yeah.
Thank you.
I'm glad someone recognized the genius behind that.
What's the intern's name?
David.
Name is David.
YouTube comments will rage Oliver's bait, for sure.
I mean, they always try to bait my rage.
Or rage the bait.
I don't even know what you're trying to say.
Where's that from, Miss Maple Leafs?
My name is David.
That is my name.
I feel like I've heard something like that before that that is my name.
Is that from a movie?
If...
No, Five Nights at Freddy's fansaw.
Okay, then I don't know.
Maybe that's, you know, inspired by something else.
The auto-poop is his favorite item.
What is the auto-poop?
Oh, the one where you poop while holding the button.
No, no, no.
That is terrible.
Unless you have pyromancy.
Then it's good.
Then it's actually quite amazing.
Dude, imagine that, that's infinite healing.
I guess it's the same as infinite healing as when you get the fetus.
Yeah, both of those are S tier together with the pyromancy.
Have you tried games similar to WoW?
Well, I've tried retail WoW and it didn't quite scratch the same itch.
I have tried, I think I tried Guild Wars very briefly many, many years ago.
Did not even catch my attention at all.
It was just like, I was just like, this is not WoW.
I guess I was looking for WoW, you know.
I did play RuneScape when I was in high school.
No, no, before that, when I was like 13 years old or something.
You know, in the school computer room, we always sit there and play some RuneScape, although I don't remember shit from that game.
But that was kind of similar, I would say.
You know, the grindiness of it is comparable to the amazing grind feeling of World of Warcraft.
Yeah, speaking of WoW and just, you know, Blizzard games, I was thinking of doing something completely different next on YouTube.
Like, playing Diablo 1, you know.
And then getting the Diablo 1 manual from the game as an overlay, and play the game while reading the manual like people would do back in the day.
You know, and then go over to Diablo 2 and do the same thing.
I mean, I played some Diablo 2 before, but I don't really understood what was happening because my friend was there and he was boosting me, I think, giving me all kinds of items.
The game was over before I even knew it.
Didn't really understand shit, so I think I want to try and, you know, do it again and actually try to understand what's going on.
You tried the Diablo 2 for the first time recently?
The remastered one, right?
Would you like it?
Gio Guessers Dream.
I actually did that one once before.
Spoiler alert, I'm terrible at it.
Like, you can put me in the middle of Copenhagen and I wouldn't be able to tell you that it's Copenhagen.
I would be like, this is this random town in France.
What character do you think you've played the least?
Definitely Azazel.
That's why I'm trying to play some more Azazel, you know?
But I gotta get that Azazel number up.
It's way too far behind.
Will you try Persona?
I have tried Persona.
I played some of Persona 5.
Never did complete it, but I got pretty far.
I would say, by my estimation, maybe like 60% through the game.
And I loved it.
But it was so long.
I kinda burned out on it a little bit.
You did get Denmark, and you did recognize it was Denmark in Runwright.
Oh, okay.
I guess when I see a flat terrain and a lot of fields, I just go, that looks like where I live.
So it helps.
You played the Azazel on your phone with Switch Simulator?
Wait, you had a Switch Simulator on your phone?
Does that even run well?
I would think that's not gonna run well.
Is the phone strong enough to even emulate that?
60 frames?
Wow!
Holy shit.
Does the game music normally warble like this?
Oh, if that's happening to you, that's on Twitch.
You need to F5?
And then Alt-F4.
No, no, not the last part, but F5 just refreshed the stream.
It's a Twitch issue.
It happens to me too when I watch streams.
It's super annoying.
I don't know why they haven't fixed it yet.
It's been like this for years.
Many, many years.
Speaking of music, hold on.
And speaking of Persona.
Oh yeah, don't forget to the lead system 32.
That is so old.
Frank, you just revealed your true age.
Or maybe I did too with the Alt-F4.
Is this Mementos?
It is, yep.
Music that plays when you go into Mementos.
System 33?
No, no, no.
System 33 failed.
It's time for System 32.
Yeah, they didn't make it.
It was not the run.
Man, that was brilliant.
But thank you for, you know, passing the brilliancy to me with that one.
You told us we can vote the stream on what to do.
Fuck, you're right, Doggy Bird.
I forgot about that.
Let's write that down for next time.
To-do list, make a vote and have people decide the next activity in Isaac.
Let's make it like this so I won't forget it.
Thank you for reminding me.
Totally forgot about that.
We didn't get any seeds to stream?
Oh my god, you're so right.
Let me go ahead and write that down.
Make sure to provide seeds next time.
Anything else, guys?
What else did I forget?
You're right, I forgot both of those.
I mean, sometimes I press escape, right?
And you can maybe get it from there, right?
You have- oh yeah, you're making a spreadsheet.
That's right.
That's gonna be so cool to look at, at the end.
You didn't give us the digits on the bag of your credit card.
Give digits on credit cards.
Oh yeah, good idea, actually.
Also, play some more Isaac.
Isaac is good for the soul.
I feel like I'm getting pretty good.
Like, I'm getting more consistent wins here.
Or at least just getting pretty far in every run.
It's very rare that I die within the last- or first three floors, like I did in the beginning.
Like, the first three floors were...
That was a battlefield at first.
We should definitely react to the very first stream that I did in this game at some point.
Maybe towards the very end.
Just like we did in Minecraft, you know?
That's gonna be fun.
I really want to see how I did on the first time.
You'd bring spit yourself?
I'm immune to that.
Like, I don't know.
Maybe not with myself, but when I watch other streamers, I really don't care about that.
Because I almost exclusively watch people play games blind, and I don't know, it's not that hard for me to put myself in their shoes and realize that the reason they're being this way is because they don't know anything about the game.
If you just put yourself in someone else's shoes, just try to think from that perspective.
Mostly, I just enjoy it when they die to something stupid.
I think it's fun.
Just haven't found your own rage bait trigger.
I guess one of the triggers could be if people try to gaslight me into thinking that I actually did enjoy something I didn't enjoy.
Gaslighting is the worst when it's actually not, you know, a joke.
Or when people do it for serious.
Like, gaslighting like that is the worst.
I hate that.
It says 1 5th...
Yeah, so the stream crashed halfway through and got back up.
That's why the timer is 1 50.
I've actually been streaming for four and a half hours now.
Which means it's time to go eat food.
Yeah, we're about to end now.
Hey, your name is Blue Baby.
Bibi.
Did you change your name for this or...
Or maybe you've always been Blue Baby.
Yeah, Bronze Master.
I legitimately was confused when I killed Mom the first time.
I was like, really?
That's it?
It was just weird to me that they would show credits.
That's all.
Like, I understand that it's a, you know, a...
Dude, I want to say Rage Big.
No, it is a...
What's it called?
Rogue-like, right?
So you play it again and again.
That's the whole point.
But I was like, damn, this is not a lot to, you know, to switch things up in.
But, you know, I was wrong, of course.
You're a rogue, Luke.
Rogue-like, yeah.
Yeah, the credits is weird.
I feel like they should not show the credits every time and only show credits when there's actually credits, you know, when you have completed the game.
The cutscenes are fine.
That's just weird that the credits are running.
Well, that's just me, I guess.
Does the game get repetitive being a rogue-like?
Not yet!
This is the beauty of rogue-likes.
I'm continuously impressed at how different each and every run is.
For example, the one in the green mode, where I was shooting lasers in five different directions and I'm just spinning them around like crazy.
That was just like, what the hell?
And then you start to, you know, shoot bombs instead and there's little V-code technique.
And now I'm just using my minions to shoot things instead of myself.
There's so many different things.
It's always different.
I mean, at some point, it's gonna not be different all the time than I've seen it all.
But so far, it's been a fantastic ride.
It's also the perfect stream game.
Bronze Master, I can't stream in 4K on Twitch.
As simple as that.
I would if I could.
There is a way to stream in 2K on Twitch.
But if I have to do that, then I have to encode all the streams myself.
Meaning my computer.
So every 720p, 480p, 1080p, 4K...
No, sorry, not 4K.
2K, all of those different streams are being encoded on my own computer.
Not on Twitch's servers.
Which is really bringing my computer down, you know?
So that's why.
Theory about the door that opens with the golden key that is related to the key you can make by stepping somehow.
I think it's like a multi-stage operation.
Where I have to do a series of things in a certain order, maybe.
And then I have to maybe get the right floor type.
You know, sometimes it's flooded.
Other times it's, you know, a different floor.
And maybe I can find something there.
I know there's special rooms like that room with the bed inside of it, right?
And the desk and all that.
So there's all kinds of little weird things like that.
Where I think it's connected.
Yeah.
Any Isaac theories?
I don't know.
That's a very vague question.
I don't think I have any more theories than I've already talked about.
Yeah, I don't know why YouTube is going so crazy lately.
Like people are super toxic in some of those comments.
Not everyone.
Most guys are nice.
Just making that clear.
But it's either like spoilers or just being mean.
Like completely mean for no reason.
Or not for no reason, I guess.
But it's just a reason that doesn't make sense to me, you know.
I think it's secretly bald.
I don't know why that was so funny.
Secretly bald.
Like he's walking around with like a hat or something.
Have you seen that subreddit?
Where people encourage each other to shave off their hair?
And they have this meme where they, you know, where they put the hand on the shoulder and stuff.
That whole thing is just hilarious.
I'm telling you, if I start to bald, I'm taking it all off immediately.
Like I'm not gonna be like half bald.
No way, I'm going full bald if it happens.
And then I'm gonna grow a huge beard.
And become like a viking.
A very lanky looking viking with no muscles, mind you.
And a dad bod.
Easy to say when you're not balding.
No, but really, I would do it.
Maybe I wouldn't be a fan of it.
Like the idea of, you know, going bald.
But I would prefer that for sure.
Just rip off the band-aid, you know.
Like, having seen so many pictures on that subreddit of people going from, you know, 5 out of 10 to 10 out of 10 by taking off their hair.
I'm like, you know what?
Maybe it's time.
Even though I'm not even going bald.
I definitely have a receding hairline, but we're not quite in the bald territory yet.
All right, guys, I'm out of here.
This was a fun stream.
It was good to be back at it.
More streams coming.
And some YouTube stuff, of course.
I'm still thinking about that one.
But yeah, thanks for watching, guys.
This was great.
See ya.